<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Daily News Titles</title>
<link>https://yourusername.github.io/</link>
<description>News titles from past 24 hours (grouped by section)</description>
<lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 10:00:13 +0600</lastBuildDate>
<item>
<title>Bangla Editorials #1</title>
<description><![CDATA[<ul><li>জলাতঙ্কমুক্ত বাংলাদেশ গড়া হোক আমাদের প্রতিশ্রুতি</li><li>পেঁপে পাতার চিকিৎসা: আশা, গুজব ও বাংলাদেশের ডেঙ্গু সংকট</li><li>প্রবীণদের নেতৃত্বে প্রয়োজন স্থানীয় ও বৈশ্বিক পরিবর্তন</li><li>অর্থনীতিতে ধীরে হলেও গতি আসছে, সুষ্ঠু ধারা ফেরানো মূল চ্যালেঞ্জ</li><li>বেসরকারি বিশ্ববিদ্যালয়ে গবেষণায় অনাগ্রহ, উচ্চশিক্ষার ধারণার সাথে সাংঘর্ষিক</li><li>কার ইশারায় অশান্ত পার্বত্য অঞ্চল</li><li>পাহাড়ে অশান্তির নেপথ্যে ষড়যন্ত্র</li><li>জুলাই আন্দোলনকারীদের মারা মব নয়!</li><li>দুর্গাপূজার শক্তিশালী অর্থনৈতিক বিস্তার</li><li>সরকারি কর্মকর্তাদের অসাধু চক্রকে ধরুন</li><li>ট্রাম্প যেভাবে রোহিঙ্গা গণহত্যায় হাওয়া দিচ্ছেন</li><li>ট্রাম্পের পরিকল্পনায় কি হামাস রাজি হবে</li><li>রাজনীতি থেকে কি হারিয়ে যাবেন নারীরা</li><li>দুর্গা সত্য ও সুন্দরের প্রতীক</li><li>শারদীয় দুর্গোৎসব</li><li>উচ্চশিক্ষিত বেকার তরুণ: সম্পদের অপচয়, তারুণ‍্যের হতাশা</li><li>পাহাড়ে ষড়যন্ত্রকারীদের কোনোভাবেই প্রশ্রয় দেয়া যাবে না</li><li>স্টার্টআপ : তরুণদের আত্মনির্ভরশীল হওয়ার নতুন দিগন্ত</li><li>নির্বাচন নিয়ে কোনো টালবাহানা চলবে না</li><li>তথ্য প্রযুক্তি / 
                                             চলচ্চিত্র নির্মাণে কৃত্রিম বুদ্ধিমত্তার সম্ভাবনা</li><li>রাজনীতি / 
                                             ভাঙনের পথ থেকে তারুণ্যকে বেরিয়ে আসতে হবে</li><li>নির্বাচন পর্যবেক্ষক সংস্থা / 
                                             শুধু গ্রন্থে নহে, গোহালেও থাকুক</li><li>জনস্বাস্থ্য / 
                                             তামাক নিয়ন্ত্রণ আইনের অদৃশ্য ফাঁক বন্ধ হোক</li></ul>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 10:00:13 +0600</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">0049ad106592ec761634ac0352451787</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>English Editorials #2</title>
<description><![CDATA[<ul><li>Israel only has itself to blame for genocide accusations</li><li>Combat anthrax squarely</li><li>Persistent mob violence results from legacy of impunity</li><li>Green cities, resilient future</li><li>Govt services for migrant labour must improve</li><li>Open manholes and crisis of accountability</li><li>Silent flight of healthcare workers</li><li>How long can US deny Palestinians their rights?</li><li>Reviving inland waterways</li><li>Reforming civil service recruitment</li><li>A tribute to Tasnim Jara</li><li>World must act to resolve Rohingya crisis</li><li>In the age of WhatsApp, postcards still speak</li><li>Between hope and despair</li><li>Caring for the elderly</li><li>Animation industry, its growth potential</li><li>Beyond lofty targets: The structural roots of Bangladesh’s tax mobilisation crisis</li><li>Counting every life: Why Bangladesh must reform birth and death registration law</li><li>Tackling the hidden crisis of food waste for a sustainable Bangladesh</li><li>Western safeguards, Chinese momentum: Bangladesh’s search for balance and resilience in development financing</li><li>From case backlog to justice: A practical blueprint for Bangladesh’s courts</li><li>Trump’s Gaza plan is a weak foundation for peace</li><li>How the quality of leadership makes or breaks a workplace</li><li>The illusion of advantage: US reciprocal tariffs and Bangladesh’s exports</li></ul>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 10:00:13 +0600</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">acbdd149e8084f0abb3cb9d550ea769d</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Magazines #3</title>
<description><![CDATA[<ul><li>Jane Goodall, Conservationist Who Transformed Our Understanding of Chimpanzees, Dies at 91</li><li>First Treatment that Slows Huntington's Disease Comes after Years of Heartbreak</li><li>U.S. Military Continues mRNA Vaccine Research after RFK, Jr., Cuts Funding</li><li>How Genetics and Diet Helped the World’s Oldest Woman Live to 117</li><li>Engineered Microbes Pull Critical Minerals from Mining Waste</li><li>Demetre Daskalakis on RFK, Jr., Vaccine Schedule Changes and CDC’s Future</li><li>Is Life inside Enceladus? Cassini Uncovers Complex Organic Chemistry in Saturn’s Ocean Moon</li><li>Jane Goodall, dogged advocate for the natural world, has died aged 91</li><li>Evolution may explain why women live longer than men</li><li>Autism may have subtypes that are genetically distinct from each other</li><li>The mystery of highly reactive oxygen has finally been solved</li><li>'We're precipitating an extermination rather than an extinction event'</li><li>NASA's asteroid deflection test had unexpected and puzzling outcome</li><li>How brain organoids are revealing what truly makes humans unique</li><li>The best new science fiction books of October 2025</li><li>Daydream Your Way to Life-Changing Insights</li><li>New Life for Rotting Seaweed</li><li>Should We Bring the Dead Back to Life?</li><li>Quiz: Can You Guess the Stephen King Book Based on a Synonym?</li><li>10 of America’s Most Haunting Hikes</li><li>Definition Detective Quiz #57: Guess the Meanings of These Tricky Words</li><li>Bail Out Argentina</li><li>Scientists predict the universe will end in ‘big crunch’</li><li>Americans receive the most scam calls in the world</li><li>Women really do live longer than men. Here’s why.</li><li>Amazon is clearing out its most popular Kindle eReaders with these early Prime Day deals</li><li>Cat-sized Jurassic reptile had the jaws of a python</li><li>A life-long car lover recreated the Griswold’s famous station wagon</li><li>How WWII made Hershey and Mars Halloween candy kings</li><li>What to Do If You Feel Trapped</li><li>Living in the Tension of Opposites</li><li>Creating an Athletic Brain</li><li>Unmasking Control in Emotionally Abusive Relationships</li><li>From Burnout to Balance: One Mother's Mental Health Journey</li><li>How to Build, Sustain—and Destroy—Trust</li><li>Can Good Learners Judge How Well They Learned?</li><li>Renaming and Reconceptualizing Schizophrenia</li><li>Psychology, Crime, and Violence</li><li>Major Down and Up Sides of Nitrous Oxide</li><li>Is There a Link Between Economic Factors and Suicide?</li><li>The Invisible Middle</li><li>Flourishing at Work: What Is It? How Do You Get It?</li><li>Childfree by Circumstance</li><li>Break Free from Anger and Aggression</li><li>Boundaries and Compartmentalization for Existential Anxiety</li><li>Can Women Have It All?</li><li>Helping Students Become AI Literate</li><li>Cardio for the Mind</li><li>Reframing Depression: Not Mad, Not Bad, Just Old</li><li>A Brain Dial for Appetite</li><li>How to Make AI Serve Human Connection</li><li>A Blood Test for Alzheimer’s Disease?</li><li>‘Clueless’ Turns 30 and Still Speaks to Divorce</li><li>What All Bad Relationships Have in Common</li><li>Insights Into Suicide and Adverse Childhood Experiences</li><li>Mister Rogers and the Neuroscience of Kindness</li><li>How Rewilding With the Beauty of Birds Can Heal Our Planet</li><li>Who Determines What the Public Should See</li><li>Three Friendship Red Flags That Most People Overlook</li><li>An AI tool is trying to predict your risk of getting many diseases years in advance – here’s how it works</li><li>নারকেল নেমেছে যুদ্ধে: প্রাণ বাঁচায়, জীবন পোড়ায়</li></ul>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 10:00:13 +0600</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">eaef4998723ba33e184c598c25d0ee17</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>International #4</title>
<description><![CDATA[<ul><li>US offers security guarantees to Qatar after Israel strikes: White House</li><li>Mobile and internet restored across Afghanistan: AFP journalists</li><li>At least six aid boats bound for Gaza intercepted by Israel</li><li>More ingredients for life discovered in ocean on Saturn moon</li><li>China launches visa to attract foreign tech talent</li><li>US Senate rejects plan to end government shutdown</li><li>Philippines quake death toll rises to 69, official says</li><li>Greta Thunberg says people aboard Global Sumud Flotilla aren’t ‘terrorists’ after Israel launches smear campaign</li><li>Former president of DR Congo sentenced to death</li><li>Moon’s far side interior is cooler than near side, study finds</li><li>Trump says US govt will ‘probably’ shut down</li><li>South African ambassador found dead outside hotel in Paris</li><li>Pakistan, India on US watch list for human trafficking</li><li>Violence breaks out in Morocco as anti-government protests rage for fourth day</li><li>‘A life of captivity’: Canada refuses marine park’s request to export its whales to China</li><li>Caribbean nations launch EU-style deal to let citizens work freely across borders</li><li>Vanuatu open to signing deal with Australia but will not be subject to ‘bullying’ from larger countries</li><li>Philippines earthquake death toll rises to at least 69 as Cebu hospitals struggle</li><li>China replaces high-level diplomat after reported detention</li><li>Taiwan now biggest importer of Russian naphtha despite being Ukraine ally</li><li>News live: PNG approves delayed defence treaty with Australia; Commonwealth Bank outage hits customers</li><li>Revealed: YouTube’s three legal grounds for challenging inclusion in Australia’s under-16s social media ban</li><li>Mushroom murderer Erin Patterson will appeal against her convictions, court told</li><li>At least 29 Americans have sought asylum in Australia since second Trump presidency began</li><li>Corporate ‘middlemen’ mask who really profits from Australian fossil fuel projects, report warns</li><li>Israeli naval forces board pro-Palestinian flotilla 75 miles from Gaza</li><li>Russia accused of sabotaging last power line into Zaporizhzhia nuclear plant</li><li>Munich Oktoberfest reopens after man’s deadly arson attack and bomb threat</li><li>French forces board Russian tanker suspected of drone launches – as it happened</li><li>French military detain two after boarding Russia-linked oil tanker suspected of launching drones</li><li>Gaza aid flotilla: more than a dozen vessels intercepted by Israeli forces; Greta Thunberg arrested – live</li><li>Israel’s Gaza flotilla interception triggers protests, diplomatic expulsions and calls for strikes</li><li>Trump signs order promising measures, including military, to defend Qatar</li><li>Israel says ‘last opportunity’ for Gaza City residents to leave</li><li>Middle East crisis: Israeli minister says ‘last opportunity’ for Gaza City residents to flee – as it happened</li><li>Arbitrary detention victims urge Starmer to press Modi on jailed British Sikh</li><li>Sunbeds should be banned in UK, skin cancer experts say</li><li>Starmer to end asylum ‘golden ticket’ of resettlement and family reunion rights</li><li>Jane Goodall, world-renowned primatologist, dies aged 91</li><li>Met plunged into crisis amid fresh claims of misogyny and racism</li><li>Jaguar Land Rover parts makers asked by banks to put up homes as loan security after hack</li><li>Perky Maxwell House viral ad takes on housing crisis as ‘Maxwell Apartment’</li><li>White House plays racist deepfake videos of Chuck Schumer and Hakeem Jeffries on loop – as it happened.</li><li>Trump FCC chair to reportedly testify to Senate panel after Kimmel suspension</li><li>Nirvana again defeats alleged child sexual abuse image lawsuit over Nevermind cover</li><li>US citizen sues after twice being detained by immigration agents</li><li>China curbs use of Nokia and Ericsson in telecoms networks</li><li>India should not shed tears over H-1B visas</li><li>Badenoch pledges to ditch flagship UK climate change law</li><li>UK pension funds should invest more in science, says minister</li><li>Shawbrook prepares to launch initial public offering</li><li>FirstFT: Brussels backs US-style tariffs on Chinese steel</li><li>Argentine assets hit by fresh selling amid worries over US bailout</li><li>IPO of data centre developer touting Trump ties surges on market debut</li><li>UK to scrap right of refugees to seek permanent residency after 5 years</li><li>Utah-based leasing giant challenges First Brands rescue loan</li><li>US government remains shut as senators fail to agree funding plan</li><li>US private sector employers shed most jobs since 2023</li><li>Hamas confronts its final red line</li><li>UK set to exempt newly-listed company shares from stamp duty</li><li>Pope Leo contradicts Trump and calls for action on climate change</li><li>US pledges to defend Qatar against ‘any attack’</li><li>Only three UK companies declare foreign influence in new register</li><li>Going back to the 1970s won’t save Mexico</li><li>UK’s PPE Medpro win unlikely to guarantee recovery of £122mn, lawyers warn</li><li>Soul searching over threat from Reform dominates end of Labour conference</li><li>Diversified Energy to switch its primary listing from London to New York</li><li>Supreme Court blocks Trump from immediately firing Fed’s Lisa Cook</li><li>Brussels backs Trump-style tariffs on cheap Chinese steel</li><li>A long-awaited plan for ending the war in Gaza</li><li>BYD monthly sales fall for first time since early 2024</li><li>Hamas’s Worst Option, Except for All the Others</li><li>‘Spooky action at a distance’ – a beginner’s guide to quantum entanglement and why it matters in the real world</li><li>From gladiators to mock naval battles, what were the major sports events in the ancient world?</li><li>The Michigan church shooting sits within a long history of hatred against Mormons in America</li><li>New documentary about the Malka Leifer case centres trauma, persistence and survival</li><li>Dementia is now the leading cause of death in Australia. But why is it fatal?</li><li>One quiet change is about to let you export much more solar</li><li>The man who could lead an independent Palestine</li><li>Why a quick compromise to the first government shutdown in nearly 7 years seems unlikely</li><li>Jane Goodall, the gentle disrupter whose research on chimpanzees redefined what it meant to be human</li><li>What Saudi Arabia’s role in the Electronic Arts buyout tells us about image, power and ‘game-washing’</li><li>Why investment in clean indoor air is vital preparation for the pandemics and climate emergencies to come</li><li>Dangerous, overpriced, crammed full: poor housing for seasonal workers revealed</li><li>We teach kids to look after their bodies – here’s how to do the same for a healthy mind</li><li>With extra study, nurses will be able to prescribe medications. Here’s what to expect</li><li>The controversial GST deal with the states is under review. There are better alternatives</li><li>PR firms are spreading climate misinformation on behalf of fossil fuel companies. Could Australia stop them?</li><li>Childhood wealth and social status can help people get leadership roles in adulthood</li><li>The overlooked service that could make plans for a library in every primary school in England a reality</li><li>As Hamas considers a peace deal, the man most Palestinians want to lead them sits in an Israeli jail</li><li>An AI tool is trying to predict your risk of getting many diseases years in advance – here’s how it works</li><li>How different mushrooms learned the same psychedelic trick</li><li>The UK has a regional inequality problem – levelling the playing field for entrepreneurs could help</li><li>Caravaggio’s Medusa: why we need to look the Gorgon in the eye</li><li>What the gut microbiome of the world’s oldest person can tell us about ageing</li><li>Palm trees in Africa are in decline: these botanists made a plan to do something about it</li><li>Dams for development? Unpacking tensions in the World Bank’s hydropower policies</li><li>South African students still don’t feel safe on campus: how protection can be stepped up</li><li>The smartphone in Saudi Arabia: between women’s empowerment and surveillance</li><li>Bacchae is bold first choice for National Theatre’s new director</li><li>Tariffs may bring a US$50 billion monthly boost to the US government. But ordinary Americans won’t feel the benefit</li><li>My voyage to explore how Marshallese sailors find their way at sea without technology</li><li>Labour to revive maintenance grants and further education – but can it improve skills and social mobility at the same time?</li><li>‘See you in Valhalla’: how the FBI director waded into the far-right’s obsession with the Vikings</li><li>Why the politics of cancellation never works</li><li>Charlie Kirk’s legacy is the beneficiary of empathy, but he couldn’t stand the term</li><li>Violent acts in houses of worship are rare but deadly – here’s what the data shows</li><li>Many book bans could be judging titles mainly by their covers</li><li>Flood-prone Houston faces hard choices for handling too much water</li><li>Conventional anti-corruption tools often fail to address root causes – but loss of US leadership could still spell trouble for efforts abroad</li><li>From ‘Frankenstein’ to ‘Dracula,’ exploring the dark world of death and the undead offers a reminder of our mortality</li><li>Cellphones in schools – more states are taking action to reduce student distraction without eliminating tech access</li><li>Caffeine pouches deliver a fast hit – and hidden risks</li><li>Plants are incredibly sensitive – what we learned about their response system could help protect humans</li><li>Poor sleep may make your brain age faster – new study</li><li>What will it take? The sweeteners Australia could offer Turkey to snatch COP31</li><li>Australians want to spend more on space – but we don’t really know where we’re going</li><li>New data shows the US dollar still dominates foreign exchange markets – despite Trump’s economic chaos</li><li>The world is failing Gaza’s starving children, aid teams warn</li><li>Calls grow louder for more age-inclusive societies</li><li>‘Hot debates about hot topics’, a strength not a weakness, says UNGA80 president</li><li>Human rights groups urged to ‘unite more than ever’ in efforts to end racism</li><li>World News in Brief: ‘Trust crisis’ impacts vaccine rollouts, Cyberspace must ‘serve the common good’, Türk calls for lasting truce in Lebanon</li><li>Full coverage of the General Debate, as it happened</li><li>FirstFT: Brussels backs US-style tariffs on Chinese steel</li><li>Pope Leo contradicts Trump and calls for action on climate change</li><li>Brussels backs Trump-style tariffs on cheap Chinese steel</li><li>Eurozone inflation rises to 2.2% in September</li><li>Inflation and interest rates tracker: see how your country compares</li><li>EU simplification drive gets tangled in its own red tape</li><li>Denmark’s Frederiksen warns EU ‘running out of time’ to meet Russian threat</li><li>Europe will lose out to China in e-trucks without EU action, warns industry</li><li>IPO of data centre developer touting Trump ties surges on market debut</li><li>Diversified Energy to switch its primary listing from London to New York</li><li>BP’s new chair signals more asset sales and demands faster restructuring</li><li>BlackRock’s GIP nears $38bn takeover of utility AES</li><li>Taiwan becomes largest importer of Russian naphtha</li><li>Russia’s Arctic LNG 2 Ramps Up Output to Record Levels – Bloomberg</li><li>Russia to Scrap Gasoline Import Tariffs, Additive Ban in Bid to Stabilize Fuel Market</li><li>Denmark Warns EU Over Russian 'Hybrid War' as Leaders Talk Defense</li><li>France Probing Russia-Linked Tanker for 'Serious Offenses' – Macron</li><li>Russian-Installed Official Killed in Occupied Ukraine</li><li>Russia Agrees With Hegseth's 'Prepare for War to Ensure Peace' Message, Kremlin Says</li><li>Russian Children Form Human ‘89’ to Mark Anniversary of Unrecognized Annexation of Ukraine</li><li>Austria’s Raiffeisen Bank Fails Again to Exit Russia as Authorities Block Sale – Reuters</li><li>Russia Claims Fresh Push Into Ukraine's Dnipropetrovsk Region</li><li>Russia Says Situation at Zaporizhzhia Nuclear Plant Under Control</li><li>Russia Intensified Drone, Missile Strikes on Ukraine in September – AFP Analysis</li><li>‘Not a Drone Attack’: Major Oil Refinery Catches Fire in Russia’s Yaroslavl Region</li><li>Telegram Founder Durov Says He Survived 2018 Poisoning Attempt</li><li>Thailand's business sentiment edges up in September</li><li>Death toll from powerful earthquake in Philippines rises to 72</li><li>U.S. Senate fails to approve spending bill as government shutdown begins</li><li>Israeli navy intercepts Gaza-bound aid flotilla</li><li>Roundup: Italy, Greece urge Israel to ensure safety of Gaza aid flotilla participants</li><li><img src="../20251002/fd545ec62f3146978afff84ae2454576/fe9c61c6cc384495a4b9f2c8d6f0e887.jpg"></li><li>Sudan urges flood precautions as river levels continue to rise</li><li>EU leaders discuss "drone wall," Ukraine at informal summit in Copenhagen</li><li>Electricity consumption in Portugal reaches record high: grid operator</li><li>Roundup: Fighting continues across Gaza Strip as peace proposal considered: UN</li><li>Polish court approves 7-day detention of Nord Stream suspect</li><li>1 dead, 2 injured in suspected gangland shooting at Starbucks in Canada</li><li>Switzerland's glaciers shrink 25 pct in a decade as 2025 ranks among worst</li><li>8 civilians killed in RSF drone attack in W. Sudan: volunteers</li><li>U.S. vice president warns prolonged gov't shutdown will lead to layoffs</li><li>Austria inflation eases slightly in September</li><li>Gaza fires rockets toward Israel amid Yom Kippur observance</li><li>1 killed, 5 wounded in Israeli strike on S. Lebanon</li><li>Cyprus celebrates Independence Day, emphasizes reunification goals</li><li>Croatia ready to scale up drone manufacturing: defense minister</li><li>Ukraine receives 4 bln euros in EU loan from frozen Russian assets</li><li>Druze seek Sweida autonomy and turn toward Israel, adding new twist to Syria’s tensions</li><li>As outrage over the war in Gaza grows, Europe’s relationship with Israel falters</li><li>Zelenskyy and UN atomic agency head warn of heightened risk at huge Ukrainian nuclear plant</li><li>Thousands march in Serbia in persistent resistance to autocratic leader Vucic</li><li>Mystery drone sightings reported over critical infrastructure in northern Germany</li><li>Indonesian rescuers race to find dozens of students in rubble of collapsed school</li><li>Rohingya Muslims plead for help at the UN to stop the killings in Myanmar</li><li>Protests in Pakistan-administered Kashmir leave 4 people dead and over 100 injured</li><li>Hurricane Imelda pummels Bermuda as airport, schools and government offices close</li><li>Journalism association to leave El Salvador over government pressure</li><li>Inside ‘Alligator Alcatraz,’ where detainees’ uniform color is based on criminal history</li><li>A collapse at a church under construction in Ethiopia kills at least 25 worshippers</li><li>South African opposition leader Julius Malema is found guilty on gun charges</li><li>Activists from Sudan, Myanmar, Pacific Islands, and Taiwan receive human rights award</li><li>Congo military court sentences former President Kabila to death for treason</li><li>Government shutdown takes hold with mass layoffs looming and no end in sight</li><li>National parks will remain ‘generally’ open during the shutdown, but Liberty Bell doors are closed</li><li>Idaho judge bars the release of graphic photos from crime scene where Bryan Kohberger killed 4</li><li>Woman who was confronted by Michigan church gunman says she instantly forgave him for killing dad</li><li>China replaces senior diplomat as questions persist on his whereabouts</li><li>UN authorizes a much larger force to fight gangs in Haiti with new power to arrest gang members</li><li>China’s factory activity contracts for a 6th straight month as trade tensions weigh on the economy</li><li>India beats Sri Lanka by 59 runs in Women’s Cricket World Cup opener</li><li>In Portugal, the cool of the night is when some vineyards harvest grapes</li><li>Mexican authorities investigate vigilante killings of 5 in remote community</li><li>Environmentalists, politicians, celebrities recall life and influence of primatologist Jane Goodall</li><li>Canada denies Marineland’s request to export its remaining beluga whales to China</li><li>ACLU sues Puerto Rico’s government over release of immigrants’ information</li><li>Daniel Day-Lewis, pulled out of retirement by his son, finds his acting fire still burns</li><li>Photos show the destruction and rescue efforts after an earthquake in the Philippines</li><li>FIFA VP pushes back on Trump comments about moving World Cup games from ‘dangerous’ cities</li><li>Four Caribbean nations sign deal allowing citizens to move freely without visas or work permits</li><li>Confusion over Afghan internet outage after purported Taliban statement revealed as false</li><li>Pope Leo XIV takes aim at climate skeptics as he embraces predecessor’s environmental legacy</li><li>Monitoring group says appeals court in Qatar overturns conviction of the Baha’i community’s leader</li><li>Macron says a tanker off France is linked to Russia’s shadow oil fleet</li><li>Dominican authorities arrest 11 police officers in a rare move following the killing of 5 suspects</li><li>Hundreds of migrants mount protest in southern Mexico in bid to legalize status</li><li>Trump administration imposes sanctions on some Iranian people and firms after UN decision</li><li>A postman, his family, and a chair: Van Gogh museum’s surprising reunion exhibition</li><li>Ceiling collapse at landmark building in Syria’s capital kills two renovation workers</li><li>The top photos of the day by AP’s photojournalists</li><li>Italy police seize 21 suspected forged Salvador Dali artworks after show opens in Parma</li><li>Former judge is likely the next leader of the Mormon church and its 17 million members</li><li>Firm linked to UK lingerie tycoon must repay $163 million for breaching COVID contracts</li><li>Niger River boat accident kills at least 26 people in Nigeria</li><li>South Korea says US agrees to let Koreans work at sites with short-term visas and visa waivers</li><li>Swiss glaciers shrank 3% this year, the fourth-biggest retreat on record, experts say</li><li>New study adds to the possibility of favorable conditions for life at Saturn’s moon Enceladus</li><li>Police say Oktoberfest reopens after a security sweep due to a bomb threat</li><li>Thousands march in Athens against labor law changes, disrupt services nationwide</li><li>See the world in vertical: Top photos by AP’s photojournalists</li><li>From Florida’s Everglades to California’s Golden Gate Bridge, the shutdown in photos</li><li>Activists aboard Gaza-bound aid flotilla say Israeli navy has begun intercepting their vessels</li><li>Young girl in Nepal chosen to replace the current Kumari</li><li>Morocco’s youth protest for fifth night, decry World Cup spending over schools and hospitals</li><li>US military starts drawing down its mission in Iraq countering the Islamic State group</li><li>Israel has killed more than 100 civilians in Lebanon since ceasefire, UN says</li><li>3 alleged Hamas members arrested in Germany on suspicion of plotting attacks on Jewish institutions</li><li>Wall Street sets more records, but bond yields drop following discouraging data on the job market</li><li>Japan’s lead trade negotiator defends tariffs deal with the US</li><li>Australian prime minister urges China to resume iron ore imports after reported trade disruption</li><li>Europe’s top central banker says economy holding up better than expected in face of Trump tariffs</li><li>Hyundai Palisade vs Kia Telluride, a three-row SUV comparison from Edmunds</li><li>Activists say Israeli navy has begun intercepting a Gaza-bound aid flotilla</li><li>Rescuers desperately search for survivors of earthquake in the Philippines that killed at least 72</li><li>Haitians give cautious welcome to new international force approved by UN to tackle gangs</li><li>Monitoring group says appeals court in Qatar overturns conviction of the Baha’i community’s leader</li><li>Protests about Morocco’s spending on World Cup over schools and hospitals spiral toward destruction</li><li>Bondi and Hegseth rally federal agents and troops in Memphis as part of crime task force</li><li>Eileen Gu to return to mountain where she won Olympic gold to compete in Shaun White’s Snow League</li><li>Mohsin Naqvi says India is still ‘welcome’ to receive Asia Cup from him</li><li>Israel orders Palestinians to leave Gaza City, saying those who stay will be considered militants</li><li>Activists say Israeli navy has begun intercepting a Gaza-bound aid flotilla</li><li>Jane Goodall, the celebrated primatologist and conservationist, has died</li><li>Anti-foreigner sentiments and politicians are on the rise as Japan faces a population crisis</li><li>Zelenskyy and UN atomic agency head warn of heightened risk at huge Ukrainian nuclear plant</li><li>Gaza City Exodus Is Overwhelming Relief Efforts, Aid Agencies Say</li><li>In the Philippines, Search Teams Look for Survivors of Deadly Earthquake</li><li>Can This Japanese City Make Residents Put Down Their Smartphones?</li><li>I Interviewed a Doctor in Sudan. Days Later, He Was Killed.</li><li>Time Running Out for Trapped Students After School Collapse in Indonesia</li><li>Pope Leo Calls for Unity on Climate at a Divided Moment</li><li>U.K. ‘Grooming Gang’ Leader Sentenced to 35 Years for Rape</li><li>Israel Escalates Gaza Offensive as Hamas Mulls Trump Plan</li><li>Moscow Indicates Retaliation if Europe Uses Russian Assets for Ukraine</li><li>Tony Blair, Tapped by Trump for Gaza Plan, Brings Peace Expertise and Baggage</li><li>What Is Europe’s ‘Drone Wall’?</li><li>Trump Promises to Defend Qatar, a Reassurance After Israel’s Strike</li><li>Irish Hotelier Accuses Qatari Royals of Scheme to Get Free Labor</li><li>In East Timor, U.S. Retreats From Plan to Build ‘Lifesaving’ Sewage Plant</li><li>How Social Media Is Changing the Narrative of the Israel-Gaza War</li><li>‘There Will Always Only Be One Jane Goodall’</li><li>Jane Goodall’s Thoughts for a Reporter: ‘Hope Isn’t Just Wishful Thinking’</li><li>South African Politician Julius Malema, Subject of Trump Attacks, Is Convicted of Gun Charge</li><li>London Police Chief Apologizes Over Officers’ ‘Reprehensible’ Behavior</li><li>‘She Could Have Killed Me’: Scientist Survives Shark Bite to His Head</li><li>How Broken Politics Breaks Courts</li><li>Israel Intercepts Boats Headed to Gaza With Humanitarian Aid</li><li>The Global Sumud Flotilla Is Approaching Gaza. Here’s What to Know.</li><li>Bomb Threat Delays Oktoberfest in Munich</li><li>Afghan Internet Back After 2-Day Blackout Tied to Taliban</li><li>U.S. Eases Visa Restrictions on South Korean Workers</li><li>A Tech Expo Shows What China Can Make, but Not Who’ll Buy It All</li><li>The Activists and the Anime</li><li>U.N. Security Council Approves Larger Force to Fight Gangs in Haiti</li><li>Earthquake in Philippines Kills Dozens, Officials Say</li><li>Starmer Describes ‘Fight for the Soul’ of U.K. as Populist Right Rises</li><li>Did a Green Beret Unit Commit One of the Worst U.S. War Crimes in Decades?</li><li>Trump Pardon Ended Probe Into Green Beret’s Killing of Suspected Taliban Bombmaker. Was Justice Served?</li><li>Dozens of Students Are Missing After School Collapses in Indonesia</li><li>FBI cuts ties with Anti-Defamation League amid conservative backlash</li><li>Israel intercepts Gaza Sumud flotilla vessels: What we know so far</li><li>Israeli forces board Gaza flotilla, detain Greta Thunberg, other activists</li><li>Israel kills journalist Yahia Barzaq known for his newborn baby portraits</li><li>Ethiopia church scaffolding collapse kills 36 during religious festival</li><li>PSG defeat Barcelona in Champions League after late Goncalo Ramos winner</li><li>Protesters and police clash as Morocco unrest escalates</li><li>Morocco arrests hundreds of protesters as rallies turn violent</li><li>Jane Goodall, conservationist and chimpanzee expert, dies aged 91</li><li>Macron, Meloni argue for caution in responding to Russian ‘provocations’</li><li>Israel begins to intercept Global Sumud Flotilla vessels</li><li>Can Keir Starmer overcome his political challenges in the UK?</li><li>Global Sumud Flotilla sails into ‘high-risk zone’ near Gaza</li><li>Why NYC’s Zohran Mamdani doesn’t fit racial boxes – and that’s the point</li><li>US takes a stake in another firm, this time a large lithium mine</li><li>Germany arrests three men suspected of targeting Jewish institutions</li><li>Walmart to phase out synthetic dyes in its US private label food brands</li><li>Rescuers race to save survivors of Indonesia school collapse as quake hits</li><li>Supreme Court temporarily blocks Fed Governor Cook firing</li><li>Updates: Israeli forces kill 73 in Gaza; arrest flotilla activists</li><li>A history of US government shutdowns: Every closure and how long it lasted</li><li>Barcelona vs PSG 1-2: UEFA Champions League – as it happened</li><li>Mysterious, majestic; Sudan’s Nuba Mountains</li><li>Taliban denies intentionally banning internet services in Afghanistan</li><li>Why was former DR Congo president Kabila sentenced to death?</li><li>Morocco reports first deaths from Gen Z protests as violence flares</li><li>‘Taken against my will’: Israel detains 12 Malaysians on board Gaza aid flotilla</li><li>Why Asia-Pacific is rewriting terms of trade from dollar to yuan</li><li>36 killed when scaffolding at Ethiopia church collapses</li><li>World cannot ignore threat of a modernised North Korean military</li><li>US woman undresses at school board meeting to protest transgender policies</li><li>Wildlife advocate, primate expert Jane Goodall dies at 91</li><li>EU leaders back ‘drone wall’ to repel Russia after airspace violations</li><li>Trump vows to defend Qatar in event of attack, in wake of Israel’s Doha strike</li><li>Supreme Court bars Trump from immediately firing Fed governor Cook</li><li>Ocean on Saturn moon ‘ticks all the boxes’ for life</li><li>Part of New York City high-rise residential building collapses after explosion</li><li>‘It’ author Stephen King tops US school book ban list amid censorship divide</li><li>Israeli naval forces intercept aid flotilla bound for war-torn Gaza</li><li>Without the public’s trust, AI is doomed to fail</li><li>Trump’s Gaza plan: Hamas seeks changes as Israel issues ‘last’ warning</li><li>‘Huge questions remain’: Trump’s Gaza vision stirs Arab-Islamic unease</li><li>Afghanistan’s back online after Taliban-ordered blackout</li><li>Munich’s Oktoberfest briefly closed by bomb threat, deadly family drama</li><li>EU is diversifying its supply chains, but it’s still reliant on China</li><li>‘Keep us in your prayers’: Malaysian celebrities risk it all to sail to Gaza</li><li>UN Security Council approves new military force to battle Haiti’s gangs</li><li>DR Congo military court sentences ex-president to death for treason</li><li>Why has the US government shut down and what’s next?</li><li>Delta planes collide at New York airport, video shows aircraft's wing detached</li><li>Trump offers college funding deal with strings on diversity, tuition: Report</li><li>Pope Leo's ice ritual, a veiled dig at Trump and a MAGA meltdown</li><li>12 civilians killed in firing by Pak forces as violent protests paralyse POK</li><li>Salesman-in-chief? Asim Munir mocked at home over rock show with Trump</li><li>I thought it was over: Jimmy Kimmel opens up about being taken off air</li><li>Democrats did nothing to help us: JD Vance blames opposition for shutdown</li><li>Deeply ironic to lecture on human rights: India slams Pakistan at UNHRC</li><li>Canada's new advisory flags travel risks for citizens with 'X' gender passports</li><li>Russia deliberately launching attack that cut Chornobyl power, accuses Zelenskyy</li><li>White House trolls Democrats with racist deepfake videos amid shutdown fight</li><li>Over 400 arrested, 300 injured after GenZ-led protests in Morocco turn violent</li><li>Russian President Putin set to visit India in early December</li><li>Macron says tanker off France is linked to Russia's shadow oil fleet</li><li>Trump to meet China’s Xi in four weeks, discuss soy</li><li>Colombia expels Israeli diplomats over Gaza flotilla intercept</li><li>U.K. plans tougher settlement rules for refugees</li><li>FIFA pushes back on Trump comments about moving World Cup games from ‘dangerous’ cities</li><li>Musk becomes first person to hit $500 billion net worth, Forbes list shows</li><li>Israel issues ‘last’ warning for Gazans to flee main city</li><li>White House says firings ‘imminent’ as plan to reopen U.S. government collapses</li><li>Jane Goodall, primate expert and wildlife advocate, dies at 91</li><li>Morocco's youth protest for fourth night, decry World Cup spending over schools, hospitals</li><li>Israel intercepts Gaza aid flotilla; says Greta Thunberg and others are safe</li><li>U.S. Supreme Court lets Lisa Cook remain as Federal Reserve Governor for now</li><li>Trump signs an executive order vowing to defend Qatar in the wake of Israel's strike</li><li>Part of high-rise apartment building in New York City collapses, no injuries reported</li><li>Mudslide in southern Nepal claims 4 lives</li><li>At least 36 killed, over 200 injured as church under construction collapses on worshippers in Ethiopia</li><li>Taliban government in Afghanistan rejects reports of nationwide internet ban</li><li>Pope Leo XIV urges Hamas to accept Trump's peace plan for Gaza</li><li>Munich Oktoberfest fairgrounds closed after bomb threat and deadly explosion; atleast 1 dead</li><li>U.S. senators reintroduce Bill to reform H-1B, L-1 visa rules as Donald Trump fee fuels scrutiny</li><li>U.S. Government shutdown: What to expect as partisan division rules Washington</li><li>Congo military court sentences former President Joseph Kabila to death for treason</li><li>Hamas pressured from all sides as it weighs Trump's Gaza plan</li><li>Watch: 91 students still trapped after Indonesia school collapse</li><li>Watch: Pentagon chief wants ‘highest male standard’ for combat roles.</li><li>U.S. government shutdown begins as nation faces new period of uncertainty</li><li>Watch: Trump says not winning Nobel would be ‘insult’ to U.S.</li><li>White House says layoffs 'imminent' with no end to shutdown in sight</li><li>Israeli naval ships intercept Gaza-bound flotilla</li><li>Four ways this US government shutdown could end</li><li>Dame Jane Goodall remembered as a 'true hero for the planet'</li><li>A new China tech visa has caught India's attention - now locals aren't happy</li><li>Musk becomes world's first half-trillionaire</li><li>Israel 'tightens siege' of Gaza City as Hamas reviews Trump peace plan</li><li>'None of us have ever asked for special treatment' - female veterans respond to Hegseth</li><li>Billionaire populist eyes power in Czech vote but may need help from extremes</li><li>Afghans rejoice as internet returns after Taliban blackout</li><li>State of calamity in Philippines province as earthquake kills 69</li><li>Germany arrests suspected Hamas members over alleged attack plot</li><li>Chunk of NYC building collapses in possible explosion</li><li>French troops board oil tanker linked to Russian 'shadow fleet'</li><li>Hunter S Thompson's death to be reviewed 20 years on</li><li>Danish PM calls for strong answer from EU leaders to Russia's hybrid attacks</li><li>Munich Oktoberfest to re-open after fatal house fire and bomb threat</li><li>Brown bear heavyweight Chunk wins Fat Bear Week despite injury</li><li>Kenya offers reward as anger grows over failure to arrest suspected serial killer</li><li>Man suspected of ordering murder of three Argentine women arrested</li><li>South African firebrand MP Malema convicted of firing a gun in public</li><li>Deported from the US to Ghana then 'dumped' at the border: Nigerian man speaks out</li><li>Australia sunscreen scandal grows as more products pulled off shelves</li><li>Billionaire populist eyes power in Czech vote but may need help from extremes</li><li>Hurricane season brings financial fears in the Caribbean</li><li>Bowen: Momentum is the strength of Trump's Gaza plan, but lack of detail is its weakness</li><li>Sudanese city under siege: 'My son's whole body is full of shrapnel'</li><li>Jobs, travel, national parks - what impact will US shutdown have?</li><li>Gaza doctors are starving while fighting to save lives, evacuated medic tells BBC</li><li>Watch: Jane Goodall tells BBC how she became interested in animals</li><li>Jimmy Kimmel on the moment he found out he was going off air</li><li>'It's safe now': See students pulled from rubble of collapsed Indonesian school</li><li>Funfair ride breaks apart at school event in LA</li><li>Rakhine faces a hunger catastrophe: aid groups</li><li>Indian court orders doctors to fix their handwriting</li><li>9 killed in Chennai power station accident</li><li>Flash floods kill 9 in Odesa</li><li>US shutdown: What problems may Americans face?</li><li>Thousands in need of shelter after Afghan quake</li><li>Dozens killed as quake strikes Philippines</li><li>Japan's far-right party courts Trump allies</li><li>Gaza aid flotilla intercepted by military</li><li>FAA to furlough 11,000 workers amid US shutdown</li><li>Netanyahu risks coalition over Trump’s Gaza plan</li><li>Russia refuses to recognise UN sanctions on Iran</li><li>Israel interceps Gaza-bound flotilla with activists</li><li>Morocco arrests hundreds as youth protests turn violent</li><li>Trump signs order pledging US defense of Qatar after Israeli strike</li><li>US begins troop drawdown in Iraq under agreement with Baghdad</li><li>Indonesian rescuers racing against time to save students trapped in collapsed school</li><li>Trump administration halts $18 billion funding for NYC infrastructure amid government shutdown</li><li>Three suspected Hamas members arrested in Germany over alleged plot against Jewish institutions</li><li>Flotilla activists approaching Gaza say they're prepared for a possible Israeli interception</li><li>Thousands protest against labor law changes in Athens, nationwide services disrupted</li><li>World’s largest beer festival shut after bomb threat, deadly explosion</li><li>Israel bombards, kills 46 in Gaza</li><li>Harvard to run trade schools under upcoming deal: Trump</li><li>Iran toughens penalty for spying for US, Israel</li><li>Two pulled from Indonesia school collapse as rescuers race against time</li><li>Madagascar anti-govt protesters call for general strike</li><li>Pentagon chief outlines vision for US military</li><li>US judge rules Trump admin arrests of pro-Palestinian students illegal</li><li>UK to review how courts interpret migrants’ rights: Starmer</li><li>Gaza aid flotilla presses journey, accuses Israel of ‘intimidation’</li><li>Germany warns of growing drone threat as incidents multiply</li><li>Denmark warns EU over Russia ‘hybrid war’</li><li>Ethiopia church scaffold collapse kills 36</li><li>Solution to Rohingya crisis lies with Myanmar: UNHCR</li><li>Rohingya tell UN of Myanmar bloodshed, suffering</li><li>Indonesia earthquake slows efforts to rescue those trapped by school collapse</li><li>Myanmar's war-torn Rakhine faces a hunger catastrophe, aid groups say</li><li>Myanmar's food crisis and growing hunger in Rakhine state</li><li>Kremlin on Hegseth's war preparation remark: Russia is also strengthening its military</li><li>US government shutdown starts</li><li>Israeli military boards several Sumud flotilla aid boats bound for Gaza</li><li>US begins troop drawdown in Iraq under agreement with Baghdad</li><li>Brazil's Jacu bird poo-poos US tariffs as specialty coffee sector suffers</li><li>Trump sets tough path for Palestinian Authority's return to Gaza</li><li>Moldova's election faces AI-driven disinformation from Russia</li><li>Thirty boats from Global Sumud Flotilla still heading toward Gaza after Israeli interceptions</li><li>Israel calls flotilla a 'provocation', asks to change course to avoid ‘violation’</li><li>Strike called in Italy, protests flare over interception of Gaza aid ships</li><li>Gaza aid flotilla says Israeli forces have boarded vessels</li><li>US government shutdown: How it affects key economic data publishing</li><li>US offers security guarantees to Qatar after Israel strikes: White House</li><li>Oktoberfest: World's largest beer festival shut after bomb threat, deadly explosion</li><li>Gold hits record high on US government shutdown, Fed rate cut bets</li><li>Myanmar's war-torn Rakhine state faces a hunger catastrophe, aid groups say</li><li>Gaza flotilla organisers say Israeli vessels intimidated its boats as it nears blockade</li><li>Meet Tilly Norwood: the AI 'actress' Hollywood unions are condemning</li><li>South Africa's ambassador to France found dead in Paris</li><li>China eyes US-Russia Arctic thaw for polar strategy possibilities</li><li>World cannot ignore threat of a modernised North Korean military</li><li>Xi-Trump phone call, Beijing’s military parade: 7 US-China relations reads</li><li>Trump’s China tariffs seen as ‘status quo’ amid TikTok talks, other issues</li><li>US image, morale of China team could suffer after government shutdown: analysts</li><li>Chinese coastguards ‘committed to sacred mission’ in Scarborough Shoal dispute</li><li>Europe, US still seek common ground on China, despite other policy differences</li><li>Beijing issues paper on Taiwan, rebukes West for ‘gross violation’ of global order</li><li>US$1.4 billion Tazara rail deal puts China on fast track to Africa’s Copperbelt</li></ul>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 10:00:13 +0600</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">8c74079165a9594340896fcc1bd451f5</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Geopolitics #5</title>
<description><![CDATA[<ul><li>Immigration and Tariff Policies Stunt US Economy</li><li>Jane Goodall, the gentle disrupter whose research on chimpanzees redefined what it meant to be human</li><li>Saudi-Pakistan Defense Deal: Rewiring the Kingdom’s Gulf Strategy</li><li>The Trump plan for Gaza deserves praise</li><li>The eccentric investment strategy that beats the rest</li><li>A Looming Crisis for the U.S. Military</li><li>Under Trump, American Grand Strategy Is Flying Blind</li><li>Europe Can No Longer Ignore That It’s Under Russian Attack</li><li>How America Started WWIII</li><li>Will California Zionise K-12 Education?</li><li>Crimes Against Humanity With Impunity</li><li>Mexico Must End Cash Dependence</li><li>Science Needs a New Social Compact</li><li>Trump Is Losing His Geoeconomic War</li><li>Restoring Public-Sector Capacity Where It Counts</li><li>PR firms are spreading climate misinformation on behalf of fossil fuel companies. Could Australia stop them?</li><li>Plants are incredibly sensitive – what we learned about their response system could help protect humans</li><li>Your primer on the Czech Chamber of Deputies elections</li><li>Tannebaum was interviewed by Bloomberg on US sanctions power amid Russian violations of NATO airspace</li><li>Lichfield cited in Les Echos on Russia’s motivations in Ukraine despite economic downturn</li><li>Lipsky quoted in POLITICO on the Trump administration’s steel and aluminum tariff negotiations</li><li>Lipsky quoted in The Economist on the yuan’s role in international payment systems</li><li>Trump Tariff Tracker cited in Forbes on website recommendations to track Trump tariffs</li><li>Plight of Belarusian political prisoners must not be forgotten</li><li>Former Senegalese President Macky Sall on designing an international architecture with Africa in mind</li><li>When Trump says Ukraine can win back all territory taken by Russia, he’s not wrong</li><li>Applying a national security lens to the International Court’s climate change opinion</li><li>Australia’s AI choice: Standards setter or technology taker?</li><li>When the Taliban switches off the internet, Afghanistan disappears</li><li>China replaces senior diplomat as questions persist on his whereabouts</li><li>What it really means to be pro-life - Pope intervenes in US abortion debate</li><li>Hybrid war on Europe—why is Denmark the first line of defence?</li><li>Europe and America in the world of yesterday</li><li>Will a Trump-Blair New Gaza fiefdom point the way to a Palestinian state?</li><li>It’s time for a new boost to EU-India relations</li><li>When Beijing makes a climate pledge, the world should listen</li><li>US shutdown will leave a world of hurt even if it ends quickly</li><li>The world is heading toward a digital tech crisis</li><li>The many holes in ‘Doughnut Economics’</li><li>Trump’s Gaza plan may be as good as it gets for Hamas</li><li>Typhon in Japan changes the game — and China knows it</li><li>Trump’s big, costly, coercive trade deals falling apart in Asia</li><li>Reports of the dollar’s death are premature</li><li>Russia quietly arming China’s paratroopers for Taiwan fight</li><li>Why America’s ‘Unusual’ Democracy Leads to Shutdowns</li><li>What Unrest in Ladakh Means for New Delhi</li><li>How a U.S. Government Shutdown Could Impact Washington’s Foreign Policy</li><li>Can a European Drone Wall Stop Russia?</li><li>Why Is Trump Bailing Out Argentina’s Milei?</li><li>Trump’s Speech to Generals Was Incitement to Violence Against Americans</li><li>How Trump Could Get Bagram Back</li><li>The U.S. Should Not Bail Out Argentina</li><li>Inside Lebanon’s Audacious Disarmament Plan</li><li>The Evolution of How We Interpret (and Misinterpret) AI</li><li>When Biology Meets the Battlefield: An Interview with Diane DiEuliis</li><li>Flood the Zone: III Marine Expeditionary Force’s Mobility Mandate</li><li>Explaining Trump’s Surprising Turn to Pakistan</li><li>Turkistan Islamic Party Threatens Security of States in South and Central Asia</li><li>Indian Railways Achieve Milestone by Connecting Remote Northeastern State</li></ul>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 10:00:13 +0600</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">5f731171872afc824645b74697fa8b2b</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>