<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Bangla Editorials</title><link>https://evilgodfahim.github.io/</link><description>Bangla Editorials - Last 24 hours</description><item><title>আস্থা সংকটে উদ্যোক্তারা, গতি নেই অর্থনৈতিক পুনরুদ্ধারে</title></item><item><title>পিআরের দাবিতে আন্দোলন নির্বাচন পেছানোর কৌশল</title></item><item><title>রোহিঙ্গা প্রত্যাবর্তনে জাতিসংঘের সম্মেলন কি ভূ–রাজনীতিকে প্রভাবিত করবে?</title></item><item><title>নেপালে বিক্ষোভের নেপথ্যে দুর্নীতি নয়, ভূ-রাজনীতি</title></item><item><title>রাজনৈতিক কারণে ইমেজ সংকটে বাংলাদেশ</title></item><item><title>মূল্যস্ফীতি, খাদ্যভোগ এবং উৎপাদন</title></item><item><title>নির্বাচন প্রশ্নে চাই জাতীয় ঐক্য</title></item><item><title>রাজনীতিতে ইতিবাচক পরিবর্তন আসতেই হবে</title></item><item><title>বাড়ছে গুজব ও অপতথ্য</title></item><item><title>দক্ষিণ এশিয়ার ভূ-রাজনৈতিক হিসাব-নিকাশ</title></item><item><title>সেনা সাফল্যে খেই হারানো গুজববাজরা ফের সক্রিয়</title></item><item><title>নির্বাচনের আগে অর্থনৈতিক পরিকল্পনা জানান</title></item><item><title>সংক্ষুব্ধ মানুষ, কিন্তু প্রকাশের পথ পাচ্ছে না</title></item><item><title>দেশের রাজনৈতিক সংস্কৃতিতে অশ্লীল গালিগালাজ</title></item><item><title>ভোক্তার ন্যায্য অধিকার: বাজারে স্বচ্ছতা আনতে প্রয়োজন আইন সংস্কার</title></item><item><title>বাংলাদেশ ব্যাংকের নীতি সহায়তা আরো সহজ করা প্রয়োজন</title></item><item><title>পাহাড়ে অশান্তির বিষ টার্গেট সেনাবাহিনী</title></item><item><title>আদর্শ প্রস্তুতি ছাড়া ক্রিকেট বিশ্বকাপে নারী দল</title></item><item><title>পেঁপে পাতার চিকিৎসা: আশা, গুজব ও বাংলাদেশের ডেঙ্গু সংকট</title></item><item><title>প্রবীণদের নেতৃত্বে প্রয়োজন স্থানীয় ও বৈশ্বিক পরিবর্তন</title></item><item><title>ইসলামী ব্যাংকের হারানো গৌরব পুনরুদ্ধারের উপায়</title></item><item><title>উৎপাদিত শস্যের এক-তৃতীয়াংশ অপচয়, খাদ্যনিরাপত্তা নিশ্চিতে বাধা</title></item><item><title>বড়াইগ্রামে জলাবদ্ধতায় ২০০ পরিবার, পানি নিষ্কাশনে উদ্যোগ নিন</title></item><item><title>ট্রাম্পের পরিকল্পনা কতটা শান্তি আনবে</title></item><item><title>পরিবর্তনের ধারায় বৈশ্বিক রাজনীতি</title></item><item><title>শামসুদ্দীন ইলিয়াস শাহ : শক্তি, সংস্কার ও স্বশাসনের কাঠামো</title></item><item><title>দুর্গাপূজার শক্তিশালী অর্থনৈতিক বিস্তার</title></item><item><title>রাজনীতি থেকে কি হারিয়ে যাবেন নারীরা</title></item><item><title>আফগানিস্তান ও শরিয়াহ প্রসঙ্গ: আমার শিক্ষক মামুনুল হকের কাছে কয়েকটি প্রশ্ন</title></item><item><title>বিহারের ভোটের আগে মোদির জিএসটি রাজনীতি</title></item><item><title>ব্যাংক একীভূত করার উদ্যোগ আদৌ ফল দেবে কি</title></item><item><title>সরকারি কলেজে শিক্ষার হযবরল অবস্থা</title></item><item><title>প্রবীণদের প্রতি দায়িত্ববোধ</title></item><item><title>আবার সেই সমন্বয়ক</title></item><item><title>শিক্ষা উপদেষ্টার প্রতি খোলাচিঠি</title></item><item><title>জাতীয় নিরাপত্তা, অখন্ডতা ও গণতান্ত্রিক অগ্রযাত্রায় প্রয়োজন ইস্পাত কঠিন জাতীয় ঐক্য</title></item><item><title>জিয়াউর রহমানের বাংলাদেশি জাতীয়তাবাদ : আত্মপরিচয়, ঐক্য ও অন্তর্ভুক্তির দর্শন</title></item><item><title>জামায়াত নেতার অপ্রয়োজনীয় বক্তব্য দেশের ভাবমর্যাদা ক্ষুণ্ণ করেছে</title></item><item><title>সাক্ষাৎকার / 
                                             ফিলিস্তিন রাষ্ট্রের প্রতীকী স্বীকৃতি সমাধান দেবে না</title></item><item><title>শিক্ষাঙ্গন / 
                                             ঢাকা সেন্ট্রাল ইউনিভার্সিটি: শিক্ষা সংকোচনের বিপজ্জনক পথ</title></item><item><title>উত্তপ্ত খাগড়াছড়ি / 
                                             বিক্ষোভের কারণ বিবেচনা করুন</title></item><item><title>প্রতিবেশী / 
                                             শীতাতপ কক্ষ থেকে লাদাখ বোঝা যাবে না</title></item></channel><channel><title>English Editorials</title><link>https://evilgodfahim.github.io/</link><description>English Editorials - Last 24 hours</description><item><title>Youth as Driving Force for Transforming Agriculture from traditional to High-tech</title></item><item><title>Give much-needed fillip to toy sector</title></item><item><title>Recognising informal workers is a test of reform</title></item><item><title>Export processing and economic zones</title></item><item><title>Persistent mob violence results from legacy of impunity</title></item><item><title>Why accountability in Gaza is global imperative</title></item><item><title>Green cities, resilient future</title></item><item><title>Reading between the lines</title></item><item><title>Open manholes and crisis of accountability</title></item><item><title>Chattogram poses no threat to anyone</title></item><item><title>How long can US deny Palestinians their rights?</title></item><item><title>Finance adviser’s remark, rather, reeks of fascist traits</title></item><item><title>In the age of WhatsApp, postcards still speak</title></item><item><title>Between hope and despair</title></item><item><title>Korean labour market: Why Bangladesh fails to fill quota</title></item><item><title>Can Bangladesh turn carbon into cash?</title></item><item><title>Tackling irregularities, corruption in health sector</title></item><item><title>UNGA Resolution 2758 brooks no challenge and Taiwan's sovereignty is unquestionable</title></item><item><title>Bangladesh charts a course for shipbuilding excellence</title></item><item><title>Trump’s Gaza plan is a weak foundation for peace</title></item><item><title>How the quality of leadership makes or breaks a workplace</title></item><item><title>Amid rising abuse, we must take better care of our children</title></item><item><title>How to overcome the impasse on July Charter</title></item><item><title>&lt;span class="color-red"&gt;International Day of Older Persons&lt;/span&gt; / Dhaka is not for old people, but it is their city too</title></item></channel><channel><title>Magazines</title><link>https://evilgodfahim.github.io/</link><description>Magazines - Last 24 hours</description><item><title>Engineered Microbes Pull Critical Minerals from Mining Waste</title></item><item><title>Demetre Daskalakis on RFK, Jr., Vaccine Schedule Changes and CDC’s Future</title></item><item><title>Is Life inside Enceladus? Cassini Uncovers Complex Organic Chemistry in Saturn’s Ocean Moon</title></item><item><title>Is Tylenol Safe for Children? What Research Shows About Acetaminophen</title></item><item><title>Rock Art Discovery Reveals Unknown Arabian Nomads from 12,000 Years Ago</title></item><item><title>Are We Alone? NASA’s Habitable Worlds Observatory Aims to Find Out</title></item><item><title>The best new science fiction books of October 2025</title></item><item><title>We now know why a belly button becomes an 'innie'</title></item><item><title>Egg cells made with DNA from human skin fertilised in the lab</title></item><item><title>'Funny' videos of stressed and frightened pets are no laughing matter</title></item><item><title>Ancient artists created giant camel engravings in the Arabian desert</title></item><item><title>The exceptionally tasty new fermented foods being cooked up in the lab</title></item><item><title>New Life for Rotting Seaweed</title></item><item><title>Should We Bring the Dead Back to Life?</title></item><item><title>10 TV Shows That Were Canceled After A Single Episode</title></item><item><title>This Ingenious Trick Lets You Paint Your Ceiling Without Splatter</title></item><item><title>How to Keep a Commonplace Book: The Renaissance-Era Practice That’s Making a Comeback</title></item><item><title>Pete Hegseth Is Living the Dream</title></item><item><title>A Prophet’s Diagnosis</title></item><item><title>A life-long car lover recreated the Griswold’s famous station wagon</title></item><item><title>How WWII made Hershey and Mars Halloween candy kings</title></item><item><title>Breville early Amazon Prime Day deals: Treat yourself to a high-end espresso machine or smart oven</title></item><item><title>1,500th discovered bat species is a ‘god of the island’</title></item><item><title>Buy a vintage military airplane for $25</title></item><item><title>Sea sponges may have been Earth’s first living creatures</title></item><item><title>Camels depicted in 12,000-year-old rock art</title></item><item><title>Hug Your Male Friends More</title></item><item><title>5 Questions for Setting Limits and Imposing Consequences</title></item><item><title>Does the Hurt of Being Ghosted Make Us Impulsive?</title></item><item><title>Why It’s So Hard to Take a Break—Even When We Know We Should</title></item><item><title>Inflation Hits Different for Men vs. Women, But Why?</title></item><item><title>From Heartbreak to Healing</title></item><item><title>The Path to Learning: Practice, Pause, Repeat, Empower</title></item><item><title>Supporting Foster Parents</title></item><item><title>Is AI the New Excuse for Dishonesty?</title></item><item><title>Why You’re More Than Your Title</title></item><item><title>How Passive-Aggressive Remarks Can Damage Love and Trust</title></item><item><title>7 Things to Do to Make Your Dog Love You Even More</title></item><item><title>The Impact of Strong Friendships Across the Lifespan</title></item><item><title>Break Free From the Fear of Weight Gain</title></item><item><title>Should We Let AI Think for Us?</title></item><item><title>The One Simple Secret to Better Communication</title></item><item><title>How to Heal a Broken Heart</title></item><item><title>Embracing a Person-Centred, Strengths-Based View of ADHD</title></item><item><title>CBT for Depression: How Strong Is the Evidence Today?</title></item><item><title>Beauty Advent Calendars: The Best Trick Since Coca-Cola and Santa?</title></item><item><title>Making Friends as Adults: Reboot Connection a Swipe at a Time</title></item><item><title>The Overlap Between ADHD and Depression</title></item><item><title>The Journey From Pain to Purpose</title></item><item><title>One Type of Empathy Associated with Autism</title></item><item><title>The Perfectionist's Quest for Immature Love</title></item><item><title>The New Mental Health: Science Says It's Character Strengths</title></item><item><title>Feeling the Fall Funk? It Might Be More Than Just the Weather</title></item><item><title>Using Emotional Power to Envision the Impossible</title></item><item><title>Maybe AI Was Never a Tool</title></item><item><title>If You Don't Have Kids, What's Your Legacy?</title></item><item><title>We teach young people to write. In the age of AI, we must teach them how to see</title></item><item><title>নারকেল নেমেছে যুদ্ধে: প্রাণ বাঁচায়, জীবন পোড়ায়</title></item></channel><channel><title>International</title><link>https://evilgodfahim.github.io/</link><description>International - Last 24 hours</description><item><title>At least 51 killed in Gaza in 24 hours: health ministry</title></item><item><title>More ingredients for life discovered in ocean on Saturn moon</title></item><item><title>China launches visa to attract foreign tech talent</title></item><item><title>US government enters shutdown as Congress fails to reach funding deal</title></item><item><title>Philippines quake death toll rises to 69, official says</title></item><item><title>Greta Thunberg says people aboard Global Sumud Flotilla aren’t ‘terrorists’ after Israel launches smear campaign</title></item><item><title>India plans mega dam to counter China water fears</title></item><item><title>Former president of DR Congo sentenced to death</title></item><item><title>Pakistan wavers after Gaza deal draft ‘changed’</title></item><item><title>Moon’s far side interior is cooler than near side, study finds</title></item><item><title>Trump says US govt will ‘probably’ shut down</title></item><item><title>South African ambassador found dead outside hotel in Paris</title></item><item><title>Pakistan, India on US watch list for human trafficking</title></item><item><title>Pentagon chief slams ‘fat generals,’ says US officers should resign if they don’t support his agenda</title></item><item><title>Former DRC president Joseph Kabila sentenced to death in absentia</title></item><item><title>Caribbean nations launch EU-style deal to let citizens work freely across borders</title></item><item><title>UN security council approves new military force to fight Haiti gangs</title></item><item><title>China replaces high-level diplomat after reported detention</title></item><item><title>Philippines earthquake death toll rises to at least 69 as Cebu hospitals struggle</title></item><item><title>Taiwan now biggest importer of Russian naphtha despite being Ukraine ally</title></item><item><title>Indonesia school collapse: 91 missing and three dead as rescuers search rubble for second day</title></item><item><title>Base formulation may be linked to 21 sunscreens falling short of SPF claims, drug regulator finds</title></item><item><title>Police conduct ‘planned operation’ in Victorian town in hunt for Dezi Freeman – as it happened</title></item><item><title>Aged care waiting lists a ‘calculated denial of services’ that could be fatal, Senate inquiry warns</title></item><item><title>Government ‘deeply concerned’ about safety of Australians aboard Gaza flotilla</title></item><item><title>Albanese hopes China’s reported BHP iron ore ban ‘very much short-term’ as ASX dips</title></item><item><title>Europe ‘in most difficult and dangerous situation since second world war,’ Danish PM warns – Europe live</title></item><item><title>At least a third of EU citizens in UK report discrimination by public bodies</title></item><item><title>Jailed Georgian politicians allege links between ruling party and Iran in letter to UK</title></item><item><title>Slovakia marks ‘dark day’ as LGBTQ+ rights rolled back in parliament</title></item><item><title>Row erupts after Venice opera house hires conductor linked to Meloni government</title></item><item><title>Israeli minister says ‘last opportunity’ for Gaza City residents to flee – Middle East crisis live</title></item><item><title>Pro-Palestine flotilla heading towards Gaza ‘harassed by Israeli naval boats’</title></item><item><title>Italy to end support for international Gaza flotilla as it nears destination</title></item><item><title>Trump gives Hamas ‘three or four days’ to respond to Gaza peace plan or face ‘a very sad end’ – as it happened</title></item><item><title>Trump gives Hamas ‘three or four days’ to respond to his peace plan for Gaza</title></item><item><title>Will Labour’s fracking ban end practice in the UK for good?</title></item><item><title>Powell victory in Labour’s deputy leader contest would mean ‘division and disunity’, Phillipson suggests – UK politics live</title></item><item><title>Samaritans to push on with branch closures despite volunteers’ objections</title></item><item><title>UK government wins £122m pandemic case against Michelle Mone-linked firm over faulty PPE</title></item><item><title>Selfridges blames slump in tourists shopping for luxury goods as sales fall</title></item><item><title>New York City high-rise apartment building partially collapses</title></item><item><title>Wisconsin Planned Parenthood clinics pause abortion services amid funding crisis</title></item><item><title>Border wall slicing through Arizona wildlife corridor begins construction: ‘A show of force for nothing’</title></item><item><title>US government shutdown live: ‘erratic’ and ‘unhinged’ Trump to blame for shutdown, say senior Democrats</title></item><item><title>US government shuts down after Senate fails to advance both parties’ bills</title></item><item><title>US billionaire Josh Harris’s firm in talks for Aga cooker unit</title></item><item><title>BYD monthly sales fall for first time since early 2024</title></item><item><title>US private sector employers shed the most jobs since 2023</title></item><item><title>BlackRock’s GIP nears $38bn takeover of utility AES</title></item><item><title>Miliband tells Musk to ‘get the hell out of our politics and our country’</title></item><item><title>US naval build-up bolsters Venezuelan opposition, leader-in-hiding says</title></item><item><title>Meta to mine AI interactions to help target advertising</title></item><item><title>PPE Medpro must repay £122mn over substandard Covid gowns, High Court rules</title></item><item><title>UK makes new attempt to access Apple cloud data</title></item><item><title>US government shuts down as lawmakers fail to reach deal</title></item><item><title>Owner of Gail’s and PizzaExpress bids for Costa Coffee</title></item><item><title>How the Tories might live again</title></item><item><title>Investors embrace ‘cat’ bonds</title></item><item><title>Touria El Glaoui blazed a trail for African art. There’s still a long way to go</title></item><item><title>€2,000 bonuses and free parties: hotels enter Poland’s fertility fight</title></item><item><title>Eurozone inflation rises to 2.2% in September</title></item><item><title>The worse the UK economy, the better for employers at Budget time</title></item><item><title>Inflation and interest rates tracker: see how your country compares</title></item><item><title>Starmer finally shows conviction — but way forward is still missing</title></item><item><title>South Korea raises military spending by most in more than 15 years</title></item><item><title>Taiwan becomes largest importer of Russian naphtha</title></item><item><title>Joseph Kabila sentenced to death in Democratic Republic of Congo</title></item><item><title>Starmer says UK will ‘look again’ at international migration law</title></item><item><title>Argentine assets hit by fresh selling amid worries over US bailout</title></item><item><title>UK house prices rise more than expected in September</title></item><item><title>Hamas’s Worst Option, Except for All the Others</title></item><item><title>What’s Missing From Trump’s Gaza Peace Plan</title></item><item><title>Moscow Can’t Stop the Music</title></item><item><title>Palm trees in Africa are in decline: these botanists made a plan to do something about it</title></item><item><title>Dams for development? Unpacking tensions in the World Bank’s hydropower policies</title></item><item><title>South African students still don’t feel safe on campus: how protection can be stepped up</title></item><item><title>The smartphone in Saudi Arabia: between women’s empowerment and surveillance</title></item><item><title>Bacchae is bold first choice for National Theatre’s new director</title></item><item><title>Tariffs may bring a US$50 billion monthly boost to the US government. But ordinary Americans won’t feel the benefit</title></item><item><title>My voyage to explore how Marshallese sailors find their way at sea without technology</title></item><item><title>Labour to revive maintenance grants and further education – but can it improve skills and social mobility at the same time?</title></item><item><title>‘See you in Valhalla’: how the FBI director waded into the far-right’s obsession with the Vikings</title></item><item><title>Why the politics of cancellation never works</title></item><item><title>Charlie Kirk’s legacy is the beneficiary of empathy, but he couldn’t stand the term</title></item><item><title>Violent acts in houses of worship are rare but deadly – here’s what the data shows</title></item><item><title>Many book bans could be judging titles mainly by their covers</title></item><item><title>Flood-prone Houston faces hard choices for handling too much water</title></item><item><title>Conventional anti-corruption tools often fail to address root causes – but loss of US leadership could still spell trouble for efforts abroad</title></item><item><title>From ‘Frankenstein’ to ‘Dracula,’ exploring the dark world of death and the undead offers a reminder of our mortality</title></item><item><title>Many US states are rethinking how students use cellphones − but digital tech still has a place in the classroom</title></item><item><title>Caffeine pouches deliver a fast hit – and hidden risks</title></item><item><title>Plants are incredibly sensitive – what we learned about their response system could help protect humans</title></item><item><title>Poor sleep may make your brain age faster – new study</title></item><item><title>What will it take? The sweeteners Australia could offer Turkey to snatch COP31</title></item><item><title>Australians want to spend more on space – but we don’t really know where we’re going</title></item><item><title>New data shows the US dollar still dominates foreign exchange markets – despite Trump’s economic chaos</title></item><item><title>What is ‘ear seeding’, the TikTok trend said to treat stress and fatigue?</title></item><item><title>How people are assessed for the NDIS is changing. Here’s what you need to know</title></item><item><title>The Dixson family were great Australian philanthropists, but their wealth was built on slave labour</title></item><item><title>Kamala Harris’ candid memoir reveals her ‘ideal’ vice president – and why she thinks she lost</title></item><item><title>We teach young people to write. In the age of AI, we must teach them how to see</title></item><item><title>What Trump’s Gaza peace plan means for NZ’s stance on Palestinian statehood</title></item><item><title>When China makes a climate pledge, the world should listen</title></item><item><title>A.D. Hope called a Patrick White novel ‘verbal sludge’. New books celebrate these literary rivals</title></item><item><title>Half a century of the ‘male gaze’: why Laura Mulvey’s pioneering theory still resonates today</title></item><item><title>From frog saunas to butterfly puddles: 8 ways to turn your homes into a wildlife refuge</title></item><item><title>12,000-year-old rock art marked ancient water sources in Arabia’s desert</title></item><item><title>Health insurers are offering DNA testing to see how some medicines might work. What to know before you opt in</title></item><item><title>5 outside art projects to do in the school holidays – whatever the weather</title></item><item><title>Mushroom murders, riotous mockumentary and a surveillance thriller: what to watch in October</title></item><item><title>From today, all first-home buyers can apply for the 5% deposit scheme. Here’s what’s changing</title></item><item><title>Price check: how a public grocery chain would disrupt NZ’s supermarket duopoly</title></item><item><title>As the UK plans to introduce digital IDs, what can it learn from pioneer Estonia?</title></item><item><title>Calm in a can? Here’s what the evidence says about the chill-out drink craze</title></item><item><title>A new exhibition explores John le Carré’s writing process and what it says about his political conscience</title></item><item><title>As mining returns to Cornwall, lithium ambitions tussle with local heritage</title></item><item><title>Labour conference: Starmer takes aim at political opponents but ties his own future to Reform</title></item><item><title>UK expands chemical castration pilot programme for sex offenders – but what are the risks?</title></item><item><title>Labour’s plan for migrants to ‘earn’ permanent residency turns belonging into an endless exam</title></item><item><title>Where does the Arab and Muslim world stand on Trump’s Gaza peace plan? Expert Q&amp;A</title></item><item><title>Trump’s 20-point plan for Gaza is deeply flawed but it may be the best offer Hamas can expect</title></item><item><title>Tanzania’s ruling party has crushed the opposition – the elections are a mere formality</title></item><item><title>University ranking systems are being rejected. African institutions should take note</title></item><item><title>The UN air service that flies where no one else can</title></item><item><title>Eurozone inflation rises to 2.2% in September</title></item><item><title>Inflation and interest rates tracker: see how your country compares</title></item><item><title>EU simplification drive gets tangled in its own red tape</title></item><item><title>Denmark’s Frederiksen warns EU ‘running out of time’ to meet Russian threat</title></item><item><title>Europe will lose out to China in e-trucks without EU action, warns industry</title></item><item><title>Greek customs broker caught with €3mn cash in China-linked fraud probe</title></item><item><title>Tusk tells banks to accept higher taxes to fund Poland’s defence</title></item><item><title>BlackRock’s GIP nears $38bn takeover of utility AES</title></item><item><title>Taiwan becomes largest importer of Russian naphtha</title></item><item><title>Ovo warns of ‘material uncertainty’ over its going concern status</title></item><item><title>Berkshire Hathaway nears $10bn deal for Occidental’s petrochemical unit</title></item><item><title>Denmark Warns EU Over Russian 'Hybrid War' as Leaders Talk Defense</title></item><item><title>France Probing Russia-Linked Tanker for 'Serious Offenses' – Macron</title></item><item><title>Russian-Installed Official Killed in Occupied Ukraine</title></item><item><title>Russia Agrees With Hegseth's 'Prepare for War to Ensure Peace' Message, Kremlin Says</title></item><item><title>Russian Children Form Human ‘89’ to Mark Anniversary of Unrecognized Annexation of Ukraine</title></item><item><title>Austria’s Raiffeisen Bank Fails Again to Exit Russia as Authorities Block Sale – Reuters</title></item><item><title>Russia Claims Fresh Push Into Ukraine's Dnipropetrovsk Region</title></item><item><title>Russia Says Situation at Zaporizhzhia Nuclear Plant Under Control</title></item><item><title>Russia Intensified Drone, Missile Strikes on Ukraine in September – AFP Analysis</title></item><item><title>‘Not a Drone Attack’: Major Oil Refinery Catches Fire in Russia’s Yaroslavl Region</title></item><item><title>Telegram Founder Durov Says He Survived 2018 Poisoning Attempt</title></item><item><title>As Kremlin Boasts of Arctic Riches, Indigenous Peoples Struggle to Survive</title></item><item><title>Russia Extends Gasoline Export Ban, Restricts Diesel Shipments</title></item><item><title>St. Petersburg Crematorium to Become 'Europe's Largest' in Major Expansion</title></item><item><title>Russia’s First Children’s Drone School Opens in Krasnodar as Founder Rejects Militarization Claims</title></item><item><title>Fiji ramps up fight against illicit drugs</title></item><item><title>Major Japanese makers' confidence improves in Sept. on trade deal: BOJ survey</title></item><item><title>Lithuania plans to increase electricity trading capacity with Poland</title></item><item><title>Indian gov't approves 9.5 bln USD minimum support price for winter crops</title></item><item><title>Indonesia's trade surplus expands in first 8 months</title></item><item><title>Flash: Apartment building partially collapses in New York City, no injuries reported, authorities say</title></item><item><title>ASEAN looks forward to more cooperation with China: official</title></item><item><title>Greek workers stage nationwide strike over draft labor bill</title></item><item><title>Thailand's manufacturing sector growth quickens in September</title></item><item><title>Urgent: 5.1-magnitude quake hits Reykjanes Ridge -- USGS</title></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia, UN launch global initiative to boost cyberspace capacity</title></item><item><title>Kremlin says negotiations with Ukraine on hold</title></item><item><title>Eurozone inflation ticks up to 2.2 percent in September: Eurostat</title></item><item><title>Uzbekistan's textile exports worth 1.7 bln dollars in first eight months</title></item><item><title>Flash: Boat accident in southern Nigeria kills at least 26: local authorities</title></item><item><title>Major European companies pledge larger EU investments, urge competitiveness reforms</title></item><item><title>Laos hit by widespread flooding after days of heavy rain</title></item><item><title>ADB approves 299-mln-USD loan to finance regional rapid transit project in India</title></item><item><title>India announces measures to help exporters</title></item><item><title>AES confederation to form unified force, says Nigerien president</title></item><item><title>A weakened and isolated Hamas faces pressure to accept Trump’s peace plan for Gaza</title></item><item><title>Tony Blair’s long experience in the Middle East is both his strength and his weakness</title></item><item><title>Zelenskyy and UN atomic agency head warn of heightened risk at huge Ukrainian nuclear plant</title></item><item><title>As outrage over the war in Gaza grows, Europe’s relationship with Israel falters</title></item><item><title>EU leaders consider using seized Russian assets to fund a loan to Ukraine</title></item><item><title>South Korea’s president calls for more self-reliant military as questions arise about US commitment</title></item><item><title>China replaces senior diplomat as questions persist on his whereabouts</title></item><item><title>Activists from Sudan, Myanmar, Pacific Islands, and Taiwan receive human rights award</title></item><item><title>UN authorizes a much larger force to fight gangs in Haiti with new power to arrest gang members</title></item><item><title>Bermuda lashed by distant hurricane and prepares for the stronger Imelda</title></item><item><title>South African opposition leader Julius Malema is found guilty on gun charges</title></item><item><title>Congo military court sentences former President Kabila to death for treason</title></item><item><title>Thousands of jobs at risk in Africa as US trade deal expires</title></item><item><title>Gabon’s president’s party wins most seats in first legislative elections since 2023 coup</title></item><item><title>Democrats embrace a shutdown fight in a rare moment of unity against Trump</title></item><item><title>What happens now that a government shutdown is underway</title></item><item><title>How the government shutdown will affect student loans, FAFSA and the Education Department</title></item><item><title>Here are some effects of a government shutdown if Congress, Trump don’t reach a deal</title></item><item><title>China’s factory activity contracts for a 6th straight month as trade tensions weigh on the economy</title></item><item><title>India beats Sri Lanka by 59 runs in Women’s Cricket World Cup opener</title></item><item><title>India’s Asia Cup win over Pakistan marred by trophy presentation snub</title></item><item><title>The top photos of the day by AP’s photojournalists</title></item><item><title>At least 25 killed as a church under construction collapses on worshippers in Ethiopia</title></item><item><title>Italy police seize 21 suspected forged Salvador Dali artworks after show opens in Parma</title></item><item><title>Former judge is likely the next leader of the Mormon church and its 17 million members</title></item><item><title>Firm linked to UK underwear tycoon must repay $163 million for breaching COVID contracts</title></item><item><title>Niger River boat accident kills at least 26 people in Nigeria</title></item><item><title>South Korea says US agrees to let Koreans work at sites with short-term visas and visa waivers</title></item><item><title>Swiss glaciers shrank 3% this year, the fourth-biggest retreat on record, experts say</title></item><item><title>New study adds to the possibility of favorable conditions for life at Saturn’s moon Enceladus</title></item><item><title>Munich Oktoberfest fairgrounds closed after bomb threat and deadly explosion</title></item><item><title>Thousands march in Athens against labor law changes, disrupt services nationwide</title></item><item><title>See the world in vertical: Top photos by AP’s photojournalists</title></item><item><title>A government shutdown sparks a new wave of uncertainty, in photos</title></item><item><title>A populist billionaire is the favorite in a Czech election that could shift stance on Ukraine and EU</title></item><item><title>Japan’s central bank survey shows an improved outlook for manufacturers</title></item><item><title>Security fears shut down classes at Mexico’s top university after student killing</title></item><item><title>OpenAI’s Sora joins Meta in pushing AI-generated videos. Some are worried about a flood of ‘AI slop’</title></item><item><title>Courrèges show brings futuristic minimalism to Paris Fashion Week</title></item><item><title>Helen Mirren opens Stella McCartney’s activist, cruelty-free Paris runway</title></item><item><title>No. 2 US diplomat meets much-prosecuted West African leader after visa restrictions were eased</title></item><item><title>South Africa’s ambassador to France is found dead in Paris</title></item><item><title>Maia Sandu, Moldova’s pro-Western president, cements power after the party she founded wins election</title></item><item><title>The top photos of the day by AP’s photojournalists</title></item><item><title>Serbia arrests 11 for allegedly placing pig heads and other racial hatred acts in Europe</title></item><item><title>Tropical Storm Octave to remain at sea in the Pacific Ocean, forecasters say</title></item><item><title>Strong earthquake kills 31 people in a central Philippine region hit by deadly storm just days ago</title></item><item><title>Scientists find ancient life-size animal rock carvings in the Saudi Arabian desert</title></item><item><title>OpenAI’s ChatGPT now lets users buy from Etsy, Shopify in push for chatbot shopping</title></item><item><title>Schwarzenegger downplays Trump and backs Vatican initiative to ‘terminate’ global warming</title></item><item><title>Young girl in Nepal chosen to replace the current Kumari</title></item><item><title>A weakened and isolated Hamas faces pressure to accept Trump’s peace plan for Gaza</title></item><item><title>Trump says Netanyahu has agreed to his plan to end the war in Gaza</title></item><item><title>As outrage over the war in Gaza grows, Europe’s relationship with Israel falters</title></item><item><title>Yemen’s Houthi rebels claim missile attack on Dutch-flagged ship in the Gulf of Aden</title></item><item><title>US military starts drawing down mission in Iraq, officials say</title></item><item><title>Stocks edge lower after another discouraging signal on the job market</title></item><item><title>Japan’s lead trade negotiator defends tariffs deal with the US</title></item><item><title>Australian prime minister urges China to resume iron ore imports after reported trade disruption</title></item><item><title>Europe’s top central banker says economy holding up better than expected in face of Trump tariffs</title></item><item><title>Hyundai Palisade vs Kia Telluride, a three-row SUV comparison from Edmunds</title></item><item><title>Denmark warns that Russia is waging a hybrid war on Europe, as EU leaders gather for security talks</title></item><item><title>Indonesian rescue workers ‘racing against time’ in search for dozens in rubble of collapsed school</title></item><item><title>Cuban foreign minister says Rubio’s ‘personal’ agenda in Latin America risks Trump’s peace prospects</title></item><item><title>Morocco’s youth protest for fourth night, decry World Cup spending over schools and hospitals</title></item><item><title>Government shutdown begins as the nation faces a new period of uncertainty</title></item><item><title>Eileen Gu to return to mountain where she won Olympic gold to compete in Shaun White’s Snow League</title></item><item><title>Mohsin Naqvi says India is still ‘welcome’ to receive Asia Cup from him</title></item><item><title>Israeli strikes in Gaza kill at least 16 Palestinians as Hamas mulls its response to Trump’s plan</title></item><item><title>Zelenskyy and UN atomic agency head warn of heightened risk at huge Ukrainian nuclear plant</title></item><item><title>Rescuers in desperate search after a powerful earthquake hit the Philippines, killing at least 69</title></item><item><title>Hurricane Imelda rumbles toward Bermuda as airport, schools and government offices close</title></item><item><title>Druze seek Sweida autonomy and turn toward Israel, adding new twist to Syria’s tensions</title></item><item><title>Gaza City Exodus as Israel Expands Offensive Is Overwhelming Aid Efforts</title></item><item><title>In the Philippines, Search Teams Look for Survivors of Deadly Earthquake</title></item><item><title>Can This Japanese City Make Residents Put Down Their Smartphones?</title></item><item><title>I Interviewed a Doctor in Sudan. Days Later, He Was Killed.</title></item><item><title>Time Running Out for Trapped Students After School Collapse in Indonesia</title></item><item><title>What Is Europe’s ‘Drone Wall’?</title></item><item><title>Moscow Indicates Retaliation if Europe Uses Russian Assets for Ukraine</title></item><item><title>Tony Blair, Tapped by Trump for Gaza Plan, Brings Peace Expertise and Baggage</title></item><item><title>Trump Promises to Defend Qatar, a Reassurance After Israel’s Strike</title></item><item><title>Oktoberfest Closed Because of Bomb Threat in Munich</title></item><item><title>A Tech Expo Shows What China Can Make, but Not Who’ll Buy It All</title></item><item><title>U.S. Eases Visa Restrictions on South Korean Workers</title></item><item><title>Trump’s Gaza Plan: What We Know</title></item><item><title>The Global Sumud Flotilla Is Approaching Gaza. Here’s What to Know.</title></item><item><title>Internet Is Restored in Afghanistan After a Two-Day Blackout</title></item><item><title>Trump Administration Moves to Relax Rules on Hydrofluorocarbons</title></item><item><title>The Activists and the Anime</title></item><item><title>Night Trains, Beloved Throwbacks Tying Paris to Berlin and Vienna, Will End</title></item><item><title>U.N. Security Council Approves Larger Force to Fight Gangs in Haiti</title></item><item><title>Earthquake in Philippines Kills Dozens, Officials Say</title></item><item><title>Nicole Kidman Files for Divorce From Keith Urban After Nearly 20 Years</title></item><item><title>Congo’s Former President Sentenced to Death in Absentia</title></item><item><title>U.S. Officials See Hostage Release as Promising Sign for Deal With Taliban</title></item><item><title>Athens Democracy Forum: Freedom of Speech in Academia Is Under Attack</title></item><item><title>Athens Democracy Forum: Discontent Has Put Democracy in Jeopardy</title></item><item><title>Russia’s Military Budget Shrinks as War Costs Hit Kremlin’s Economic Limits</title></item><item><title>South African Ambassador to France Is Found Dead in Paris</title></item><item><title>Starmer Describes ‘Fight for the Soul’ of U.K. as Populist Right Rises</title></item><item><title>Inside the U.S. Special Forces: 5 Takeaways on a Culture of Lawlessness in Afghanistan</title></item><item><title>How War-Crime Accusations Against Green Berets Were Denied and Buried</title></item><item><title>Did a Green Beret Unit Commit One of the Worst U.S. War Crimes in Decades?</title></item><item><title>Dozens of Students Are Missing After School Collapses in Indonesia</title></item><item><title>U.S. Deports Planeload of Iranians After Deal With Tehran, Officials Say</title></item><item><title>How Chinese Weapons Transformed a War Between Two Neighbors</title></item><item><title>Video: Rescue &amp; recovery efforts continue after Philippines earthquake</title></item><item><title>Capturing resilience in Afghanistan</title></item><item><title>US Republicans and Democrats are at a political impasse</title></item><item><title>Peruvian police arrest suspects over livestreamed femicide in Argentina</title></item><item><title>EU leaders push to tap frozen Russian assets for Ukraine reconstruction</title></item><item><title>Is Russia’s economy at risk as oil revenues shrink?</title></item><item><title>Qatar PM talks to Al Jazeera about proposal to end Gaza war</title></item><item><title>Nearly half of killings outside Gaza City since Israeli assault began</title></item><item><title>Can Trump save Argentina’s crisis-stricken economy as he hopes?</title></item><item><title>New Trump executive order guarantees Qatar security after Israeli attack</title></item><item><title>The US government has shut down – what happens now?</title></item><item><title>What happens when the US government shuts down?</title></item><item><title>“Polarised” politics to blame for US govt shutdown</title></item><item><title>Greece labour law protests bring public transport to a halt</title></item><item><title>Starvation is a war crime. So why is it so rarely prosecuted?</title></item><item><title>Trump’s Gaza ‘Board of Peace’ promises Tony Blair yet another payday</title></item><item><title>The Taliban rejects reports of nationwide internet ban in Afghanistan</title></item><item><title>How Pakistan misread the Taliban and lost peace on the frontier</title></item><item><title>Madagascar protesters return to streets as government dissolves</title></item><item><title>Munich’s world-famous Oktoberfest suspended in Germany after ‘bomb threat’</title></item><item><title>Deadly earthquake hits Philippines: What we know so far</title></item><item><title>‘Congress members get paid, janitors don’t’ in US shutdown: Fact check</title></item><item><title>Israeli settlers burn Palestinian home, fell olive trees in West Bank</title></item><item><title>Democrats &amp; Republicans trade blame as US government shuts down</title></item><item><title>Videos capture 6.9 magnitude earthquake as it hits the Philippines</title></item><item><title>Bronx high-rise partially collapses amid gas explosion reports</title></item><item><title>‘It’ author Stephen King tops US school book ban list amid censorship divide</title></item><item><title>Gaza flotilla sails on amid Israeli ‘intimidation’, ready for interception</title></item><item><title>Without the public’s trust, AI is doomed to fail</title></item><item><title>Trump’s Gaza plan: Hamas seeks changes as Israel issues ‘last’ warning</title></item><item><title>‘Huge questions remain’: Trump’s Gaza vision stirs Arab-Islamic unease</title></item><item><title>Afghanistan’s internet blackout sparks concern, Taliban denial</title></item><item><title>Oktoberfest grounds closed as Munich police investigate explosives incident</title></item><item><title>EU is diversifying its supply chains, but it’s still reliant on China</title></item><item><title>‘Keep us in your prayers’: Malaysian celebrities risk it all to sail to Gaza</title></item><item><title>UN Security Council approves new military force to battle Haiti’s gangs</title></item><item><title>DR Congo military court sentences ex-president to death for treason</title></item><item><title>Why has the US government shut down and what’s next?</title></item><item><title>Houthis claim missile strike on Dutch freighter in Gulf of Aden</title></item><item><title>US eases visa rules for South Koreans after raid but no clear solution in sight</title></item><item><title>Ukraine warns of critical situation at Zaporizhzhia nuclear plant</title></item><item><title>Trump says Harvard deal is close, university will pay US$500 million</title></item><item><title>Trump trade chief Greer calls 55% China tariffs a ‘good status quo’</title></item><item><title>Nicole Kidman files for divorce from Keith Urban after 19 years of marriage</title></item><item><title>US begins first government shutdown in almost 7 years as budget talks fail</title></item><item><title>Colombia’s Petro fires own Beijing embassy team for ‘sabotaging’ China outreach</title></item><item><title>South Africa’s ambassador to France found dead after fall at Paris hotel</title></item><item><title>Trump says Pfizer will cut drug prices for tariff relief</title></item><item><title>Did Trump, Netanyahu trick Muslim countries on Gaza peace plan?</title></item><item><title>Portion of 20-storey apartment building collapses in New York, no injuries reported</title></item><item><title>Traitors to Ummah: Pak, Arab nations face outrage for backing Trump's Gaza plan</title></item><item><title>Trump admin overhauls Green Card interview process with stricter scrutiny</title></item><item><title>White House releases photos of Benjamin Netanyahu's apology to Qatar</title></item><item><title>Trump urges consideration for Nobel Peace Prize, claims of resolving conflicts</title></item><item><title>The Hegseth hypocrisy: Fat-shaming top generals in land of McDonald Trump</title></item><item><title>Netanyahu's apology to Qatar, phone on Trump's lap: A telling White House photo</title></item><item><title>Indian medical student found dead in Dhaka, had been expelled for cheating</title></item><item><title>Watch: Would be big insult to US if I don't get Nobel Prize, says Donald Trump</title></item><item><title>US government shuts down after senate fails to pass funding bill</title></item><item><title>Unpaid US patriots on frontline: Kristi Noem slams Democrats amid shutdown</title></item><item><title>Part of high-rise apartment building in New York City collapses, no injuries reported</title></item><item><title>Mudslide in southern Nepal claims 4 lives</title></item><item><title>At least 25 killed as church under construction collapses on worshippers in Ethiopia</title></item><item><title>Taliban government in Afghanistan rejects reports of nationwide internet ban</title></item><item><title>Pope Leo XIV urges Hamas to accept Trump's peace plan for Gaza</title></item><item><title>Munich Oktoberfest fairgrounds closed after bomb threat and deadly explosion; atleast 1 dead</title></item><item><title>U.S. senators reintroduce Bill to reform H-1B, L-1 visa rules as Donald Trump fee fuels scrutiny</title></item><item><title>U.S. Government shutdown: What to expect as partisan division rules Washington</title></item><item><title>Congo military court sentences former President Joseph Kabila to death for treason</title></item><item><title>Hamas pressured from all sides as it weighs Trump's Gaza plan</title></item><item><title>Watch: 91 students still trapped after Indonesia school collapse</title></item><item><title>Watch: Pentagon chief wants ‘highest male standard’ for combat roles.</title></item><item><title>U.S. government shutdown begins as nation faces new period of uncertainty</title></item><item><title>Watch: Trump says not winning Nobel would be ‘insult’ to U.S.</title></item><item><title>Pakistan's top leadership will decide on deployment of troops in Gaza: FM Dar</title></item><item><title>Trump says not winning Nobel would be ‘insult’ to U.S.</title></item><item><title>Trump says Harvard deal is close, university will pay $500 million</title></item><item><title>At least 91 students remain buried in rubble 2 days after school collapse in Indonesia</title></item><item><title>Yemen’s Houthis claim responsibility for attack on Dutch-flagged ship</title></item><item><title>Trump administration orders federal agencies to begin implementing shutdown plans after failure to fund bill</title></item><item><title>At least 69 people killed in Philippines earthquake</title></item><item><title>Italy to end support for Gaza flotilla as Israeli action looms</title></item><item><title>Pfizer agrees to lower prescription drug costs for Medicaid in deal with Trump</title></item><item><title>South African Ambassador found dead outside Paris hotel</title></item><item><title>U.K. police investigate ‘racially aggravated’ vandalism of Gandhi statue in London</title></item><item><title>U.S. President Trump again claims he settled ‘very big’ India-Pakistan conflict</title></item><item><title>Jobs, travel, national parks - what impact will US shutdown have?</title></item><item><title>State of calamity in Philippines province as earthquake kills 69</title></item><item><title>Danish PM calls for strong answer from EU leaders to Russia's hybrid attacks</title></item><item><title>Bowen: Momentum is the strength of Trump's Gaza plan, but lack of detail is its weakness</title></item><item><title>Oktoberfest closed in Munich after fatal fire and bomb threat</title></item><item><title>Activists say Gaza flotilla circled by Israeli warship</title></item><item><title>Kenya offers reward as anger grows over failure to arrest suspected serial killer</title></item><item><title>Brown bear heavyweight Chunk wins Fat Bear Week despite injury</title></item><item><title>Man suspected of ordering murder of three Argentine women arrested</title></item><item><title>South African firebrand MP Malema convicted of firing a gun in public</title></item><item><title>Deported from the US to Ghana then 'dumped' at the border: Nigerian man speaks out</title></item><item><title>Emily Blunt among Hollywood stars outraged over 'AI actor' Tilly Norwood</title></item><item><title>Anne visits Ukraine to support children 'traumatised' by war</title></item><item><title>Australia sunscreen scandal grows as more products pulled off shelves</title></item><item><title>No more scribbling: Indian court tells doctors to fix their handwriting</title></item><item><title>US cities should be military training grounds, Trump tells generals</title></item><item><title>South Africa's top diplomat in France found dead near Paris hotel</title></item><item><title>Sudanese city under siege: 'My son's whole body is full of shrapnel'</title></item><item><title>Gaza doctors are starving while fighting to save lives, evacuated medic tells BBC</title></item><item><title>Scientists make embryos from human skin DNA for first time</title></item><item><title>'It's safe now': See students pulled from rubble of collapsed school</title></item><item><title>Funfair ride breaks apart at school event in LA</title></item><item><title>Watch: Moment houses topple into the sea in North Carolina</title></item><item><title>Watch: One street away from collapsed school as relatives wait for news</title></item><item><title>Hegseth rails against 'beardos' and 'woke' in gathering of US generals</title></item><item><title>Unpicking Trump's Gaza peace plan map</title></item><item><title>Indian court orders doctors to fix their handwriting</title></item><item><title>9 killed in Chennai power station accident</title></item><item><title>Who is Petal Gahlot – India’s voice against Pakistan at the UN?</title></item><item><title>Flash floods kill 9 in Odesa</title></item><item><title>Hegseth slams 'fat generals'</title></item><item><title>Dozens killed as quake strikes Philippines</title></item><item><title>Japan's far-right party courts Trump allies</title></item><item><title>Brazil's Jacu bird poo-poos US tariffs as specialty coffee sector suffers</title></item><item><title>UN peace forces in Ukraine, Gaza highly unlikely: India</title></item><item><title>Myanmar's food crisis and growing hunger in Rakhine state</title></item><item><title>Pope Leo bashes ‘inhuman’ treatment of immigrants in US</title></item><item><title>Flotilla activists approaching Gaza say they're prepared for a possible Israeli interception</title></item><item><title>Thousands protest against labor law changes in Athens, nationwide services disrupted</title></item><item><title>World’s largest beer festival shut after bomb threat, deadly explosion</title></item><item><title>US government shutdown threatens jobs, travel, national parks, and public services</title></item><item><title>Philippines earthquake kills 69, rescue efforts underway</title></item><item><title>Powerful quake hits central Philippines, casualties stand at 69</title></item><item><title>Houthis claim missile strike on Dutch cargo ship in Gulf of Aden</title></item><item><title>Tony Blair’s return to Middle East role seen as both strength and weakness</title></item><item><title>Starmer calls for ‘patriotic renewal,’ accuses Farage of fueling division</title></item><item><title>Russia drone strike kills 4 in Ukraine</title></item><item><title>Israeli attacks kill 41 in Gaza, Hamas reviews Trump’s plan</title></item><item><title>New protests in Madagascar despite govt’s dismissal</title></item><item><title>Taliban internet cut sparks Afghanistan telecoms blackout</title></item><item><title>Dozens missing, three dead in Indonesia school collapse</title></item><item><title>Lingering Typhoon inflicts death, flooding on Vietnam</title></item><item><title>Maduro ready to declare state of emergency over US ‘aggression’</title></item><item><title>Muslim states join European powers in backing Trump Gaza plan</title></item><item><title>Netanyahu apologises to Qatar, promises no new strike</title></item><item><title>US sanctions on key Indian project in Iran take effect</title></item><item><title>US government enters shutdown</title></item><item><title>President Trump says not winning Nobel would be insult to US</title></item><item><title>Trump tells generals US faces ‘war from within’</title></item><item><title>Bombing kills 10 outside Pak border force compound</title></item><item><title>Myanmar's war-torn Rakhine faces a hunger catastrophe, aid groups say</title></item><item><title>Myanmar's food crisis and growing hunger in Rakhine state</title></item><item><title>Kremlin on Hegseth's war preparation remark: Russia is also strengthening its military</title></item><item><title>US government shutdown starts</title></item><item><title>Brazil's Jacu bird poo-poos US tariffs as specialty coffee sector suffers</title></item><item><title>Trump sets tough path for Palestinian Authority's return to Gaza</title></item><item><title>Pope Leo criticises 'inhuman' treatment of immigrants in US</title></item><item><title>Solution to Rohingya crisis lies in Myanmar: UNHCR chief</title></item><item><title>Moldova's election faces AI-driven disinformation from Russia</title></item><item><title>Myanmar's war-torn Rakhine state faces a hunger catastrophe, aid groups say</title></item><item><title>Gaza flotilla organisers say Israeli vessels intimidated its boats as it nears blockade</title></item><item><title>Meet Tilly Norwood: the AI 'actress' Hollywood unions are condemning</title></item><item><title>South Africa's ambassador to France found dead in Paris</title></item><item><title>Ukraine warns of critical situation at Zaporizhzhia nuclear plant</title></item><item><title>Italy to end support as Gaza flotilla says unlit vessels approached boats, prompting security measures</title></item><item><title>Tony Blair's return to Middle East diplomacy reopens old wounds and new doubts</title></item><item><title>Rescue efforts ongoing after Indonesian school collapse leaves at least 91 trapped</title></item><item><title>Indian court orders doctors to write legible prescriptions, citing patient safety</title></item><item><title>US federal government shuts down amid funding standstill</title></item><item><title>Scientists discover ancient life-size animal rock art in Saudi Arabia</title></item><item><title>US to allow South Koreans to work at sites under temp visas but clear solution elusive</title></item><item><title>Chinese coastguards ‘committed to sacred mission’ in Scarborough Shoal dispute</title></item><item><title>Europe, US still seek common ground on China, despite other policy differences</title></item><item><title>Beijing issues paper on Taiwan, rebukes West for ‘gross violation’ of global order</title></item><item><title>US$1.4 billion Tazara rail deal puts China on fast track to Africa’s Copperbelt</title></item><item><title>Marco Rubio marks China’s National Day with message of peace, prosperity from US</title></item><item><title>Race to the bottom? China thwarted as US moves on deep-sea mining</title></item><item><title>Trump trade chief Greer calls 55% China tariffs a ‘good status quo’</title></item><item><title>Colombia’s Petro fires own Beijing embassy team for ‘sabotaging’ China outreach</title></item></channel><channel><title>Geopolitics</title><link>https://evilgodfahim.github.io/</link><description>Geopolitics - Last 24 hours</description><item><title>Is European AI A Lost Cause? Not Necessarily.</title></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia and Pakistan Sign A Mutual Defense Treaty</title></item><item><title>Kamala Harris’ candid memoir reveals her ‘ideal’ vice president – and why she thinks she lost</title></item><item><title>We teach young people to write. In the age of AI, we must teach them how to see</title></item><item><title>12,000-year-old rock art marked ancient water sources in Arabia’s desert</title></item><item><title>Cheap, Accurate, Lethal: Laser-Guided Rockets Are Reshaping Global Air Defense</title></item><item><title>Saudi-Pakistan Defense Deal: Rewiring the Kingdom’s Gulf Strategy</title></item><item><title>EU Enlargement at a Crossroads in the Western Balkans</title></item><item><title>From Birthright to Buy-In: The Caribbean as a Testing Ground for Citizenship</title></item><item><title>Russian Airspace Violations Demand Firm NATO Response</title></item><item><title>Mounting Water Crisis a Major Test for Iranian State</title></item><item><title>Italy’s Mattei Plan: Geoeconomic Projection into Africa</title></item><item><title>Hybrid Warfare in NYC? Takeaways from the UN SIM Network</title></item><item><title>Rhetoric or Reality? Unpacking Lashkar-e-Taiba Terror Warnings against India</title></item><item><title>Western Allies Break Rank with Washington On Palestine</title></item><item><title>Can the West survive an age of brinkmanship?</title></item><item><title>The flashing red threat from Russia’s dark fleet</title></item><item><title>Donald Trump tries to enlist the top brass for “the war from within”</title></item><item><title>What would a shutdown mean for America’s economy?</title></item><item><title>Under Trump, American Grand Strategy Is Flying Blind</title></item><item><title>Europe Can No Longer Ignore That It’s Under Russian Attack</title></item><item><title>South Korea, Japan Pledge to Continue Strengthening Ties</title></item><item><title>US-Africa Trade Agreement Expires</title></item><item><title>What the Gen Z Protests Are Really About</title></item><item><title>Free Speech and Its Discontents</title></item><item><title>‘National Defense Strategy’: A Novel and Unlikely, but Welcome, Proposition</title></item><item><title>Why Were There Russian Drones Over Poland?</title></item><item><title>Science Needs a New Social Compact</title></item><item><title>Trump Is Losing His Geoeconomic War</title></item><item><title>Restoring Public-Sector Capacity Where It Counts</title></item><item><title>To Survive, the United Nations Must Leave America</title></item><item><title>America’s Crypto Apocalypse</title></item><item><title>Plants are incredibly sensitive – what we learned about their response system could help protect humans</title></item><item><title>When China makes a climate pledge, the world should listen</title></item><item><title>Former Senegalese President Macky Sall on designing an international architecture with Africa in mind</title></item><item><title>Putin’s dream of demilitarizing Ukraine has turned into his worst nightmare</title></item><item><title>Turkey in the changing transatlantic trade environment</title></item><item><title>Belarus dictator must not be rewarded for releasing his own prisoners</title></item><item><title>As Europe’s neutral states shift closer to NATO, Ireland approaches a turning point for its security</title></item><item><title>How a UN Security Council resolution could help end the war in Gaza</title></item><item><title>Highlights from the Transatlantic Forum on GeoEconomics, as US and European leaders reimagine transatlantic cooperation</title></item><item><title>Is the US currency rescue for Argentina positive statecraft or reckless favoritism?</title></item><item><title>Is the Baghdad-Erbil oil deal a blueprint for settlement—or a stopgap?</title></item><item><title>When the Taliban switches off the internet, Afghanistan disappears</title></item><item><title>Manila’s lonely island at the centre of Taiwan contingency planning</title></item><item><title>Australian conflict prevention – from statements to strategy?</title></item><item><title>How Trump’s $14 billion TikTok tug-of-war affects Asia</title></item><item><title>China replaces senior diplomat as questions persist on his whereabouts</title></item><item><title>Europe and America in the world of yesterday</title></item><item><title>Will a Trump-Blair New Gaza fiefdom point the way to a Palestinian state?</title></item><item><title>US government on brink of first shutdown in almost 7 years</title></item><item><title>The world is heading toward a digital tech crisis</title></item><item><title>The many holes in ‘Doughnut Economics’</title></item><item><title>Trump’s Gaza plan may be as good as it gets for Hamas</title></item><item><title>Typhon in Japan changes the game — and China knows it</title></item><item><title>Trump’s big, costly, coercive trade deals falling apart in Asia</title></item><item><title>Reports of the dollar’s death are premature</title></item><item><title>Russia quietly arming China’s paratroopers for Taiwan fight</title></item><item><title>Trump’s Gaza peace plan could revive Pax Americana</title></item><item><title>China’s cargo ban gives new meaning to BHP’s ‘Broken Hill’ origin</title></item><item><title>New Zealand: Lean into a role bridging superpowers, small islands</title></item><item><title>Hegseth ‘warrior ethos’ mistakes military might for true security</title></item><item><title>Trump’s Speech to Generals Was Incitement to Violence Against Americans</title></item><item><title>How Trump Could Get Bagram Back</title></item><item><title>The U.S. Should Not Bail Out Argentina</title></item><item><title>Inside Lebanon’s Audacious Disarmament Plan</title></item><item><title>How Taipei Should Handle Washington</title></item><item><title>As Another Leadership Election Looms, Japan’s Real Bosses Take Stock</title></item><item><title>Rohingya Noticeably Absent From U.N. Conference</title></item><item><title>The Crisis for the Women Who Make Your Clothes</title></item><item><title>U.S.-Turkish Relations Have Gotten Duller, Not Better</title></item><item><title>The Chinese Public Is Obsessing Over a Perceived Celebrity Cover-Up</title></item><item><title>How to Fix the Security Council</title></item><item><title>The U.S. Military’s Greatest Test</title></item><item><title>How America Outcompeted Japan</title></item><item><title>The Middle East That Israel Has Made</title></item><item><title>When Biology Meets the Battlefield: An Interview with Diane DiEuliis</title></item><item><title>Flood the Zone: III Marine Expeditionary Force’s Mobility Mandate</title></item><item><title>Explaining Trump’s Surprising Turn to Pakistan</title></item><item><title>Tough Tests and Uncertain Outcomes from the U.N. General Assembly</title></item><item><title>Ishiba’s Swan Song at the UN</title></item><item><title>Nepal’s Fragile Dawn</title></item><item><title>Forward Kairat: The Champions League Returns to Kazakhstan</title></item><item><title>An Anti-immigration Push Won’t Solve Japan’s Cost of Living Woes</title></item><item><title>Denuclearization of North Korea: No ‘END’ in Sight</title></item><item><title>What Is China’s Fourth Plenum (and Why Should You Care)?</title></item></channel></rss>